{
    "shorten": {
        "api": {
            "name": "Get_Question_And_Answer",
            "endpoint": "/api/v1/hotels/getQuestionAndAnswer",
            "func_description": "Retrieve the question and answer information for a specified hotel. ",
            "parameters": {
                "type": "object",
                "properties": {
                    "hotel_id": {
                        "type": "String",
                        "description": "hotel_id can be retrieved from api/v1/hotels/searchHotels(Search Hotels) or api/v1/hotels/searchHotelsByCoordinates(Search Hotels By Coordinates\n) endpoint in Hotels collection.",
                        "example_value": "74717",
                        "required": true
                    },
                    "languagecode": {
                        "type": "String",
                        "description": "To obtain the response data in a specific language, enter the languagecode. languagecode can be retrieved from api/v1/meta/getLanguages(Get Languages\n) endpoint in Meta collection.",
                        "example_value": "en-us",
                        "required": false
                    }
                },
                "required": [
                    "hotel_id"
                ]
            }
        },
        "static_response": null,
        "required": {
            "query": "I'm considering staying at hotel ID 74717. Can you provide me with any frequently asked questions and answers about this hotel?",
            "params": {
                "hotel_id": "74717"
            },
            "response": {
                "average_response_time_text": "Subject to availability at the property",
                "average_response_time_in_seconds": 2414041,
                "average_response_time": "This property usually replies within a few days",
                "success": 1,
                "q_and_a_pairs": [
                    {
                        "hidden": 0,
                        "hotel_id": 74717,
                        "answer_time_epoch": 1571923294,
                        "translated_answer": null,
                        "asked_at": "2019-10-23 13:04:42",
                        "question": "Is there a hand shower",
                        "answer": "Yes",
                        "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                        "question_id": 1489869,
                        "sign_off": null,
                        "votes": 29,
                        "naive_sentiment": 93,
                        "ask_time_epoch": 1571835882,
                        "translated_question": null,
                        "room_id": 7471705,
                        "answered_at_formatted": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                        "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                        "language": "en",
                        "answered_at": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                        "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                    },
                    {
                        "hotel_id": 74717,
                        "hidden": 0,
                        "translated_answer": null,
                        "answer_time_epoch": 1598246897,
                        "asked_at": "2020-08-24 00:35:18",
                        "answer": "Yes sir, we can provide the same subject to availability at the time of arrival.",
                        "question": "Hi i have elderly parents and they would arrive in domestic flight and would be travelling on international flight . do you offer early check in around 11am?",
                        "room_id": 7471707,
                        "naive_sentiment": 95,
                        "ask_time_epoch": 1598229318,
                        "translated_question": null,
                        "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                        "sign_off": null,
                        "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                        "question_id": 4386257,
                        "votes": 27,
                        "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                        "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                        "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                        "language": "en"
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Hello. Do you have swimming pool and is it available to use now? Best regards, Tatiana",
                        "answer": "The swimming pool is operational from 06:00 to 22:00 hours daily.",
                        "answer_time_epoch": 1653844021,
                        "translated_answer": null,
                        "asked_at": "2022-05-26 06:41:21",
                        "hidden": 0,
                        "hotel_id": 74717,
                        "language": "en",
                        "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                        "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                        "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                        "votes": 25,
                        "question_id": 25104804,
                        "sign_off": null,
                        "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                        "ask_time_epoch": 1653547281,
                        "naive_sentiment": 3,
                        "translated_question": null,
                        "room_id": null
                    }
                ],
                "opted_out_of_q_and_a": 0,
                "hotel_id": "74717",
                "collect_q_and_a_questions": 1
            }
        },
        "optional": {
            "query": "I'm planning to stay at hotel ID 74717 and would like to know the frequently asked questions and answers about this hotel. Could you provide this information in English?",
            "params": {
                "hotel_id": "74717",
                "languagecode": "en-us"
            },
            "response": {
                "hotel_id": "74717",
                "success": 1,
                "average_response_time_in_seconds": 2414041,
                "average_response_time": "This property usually replies within a few days",
                "collect_q_and_a_questions": 1,
                "q_and_a_pairs": [
                    {
                        "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                        "question": "Is there a hand shower",
                        "language": "xu",
                        "asked_at": "2019-10-23 13:04:42",
                        "answered_at": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                        "answer_time_epoch": 1571923294,
                        "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                        "hidden": 0,
                        "ask_time_epoch": 1571835882,
                        "translated_question": null,
                        "sign_off": null,
                        "room_id": 7471705,
                        "question_id": 1489869,
                        "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                        "translated_answer": null,
                        "answered_at_formatted": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                        "naive_sentiment": 93,
                        "answer": "Yes",
                        "hotel_id": 74717,
                        "votes": 29
                    },
                    {
                        "question": "Hi i have elderly parents and they would arrive in domestic flight and would be travelling on international flight . do you offer early check in around 11am?",
                        "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                        "asked_at": "2020-08-24 00:35:18",
                        "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                        "language": "xu",
                        "hidden": 0,
                        "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                        "answer_time_epoch": 1598246897,
                        "ask_time_epoch": 1598229318,
                        "question_id": 4386257,
                        "room_id": 7471707,
                        "translated_question": null,
                        "sign_off": null,
                        "translated_answer": null,
                        "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                        "naive_sentiment": 95,
                        "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                        "votes": 27,
                        "answer": "Yes sir, we can provide the same subject to availability at the time of arrival.",
                        "hotel_id": 74717
                    },
                    {
                        "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                        "question": "Hello. Do you have swimming pool and is it available to use now? Best regards, Tatiana",
                        "asked_at": "2022-05-26 06:41:21",
                        "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                        "language": "xu",
                        "hidden": 0,
                        "answer_time_epoch": 1653844021,
                        "ask_time_epoch": 1653547281,
                        "question_id": 25104804,
                        "sign_off": null,
                        "translated_question": null,
                        "room_id": null,
                        "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                        "translated_answer": null,
                        "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                        "naive_sentiment": 3,
                        "answer": "The swimming pool is operational from 06:00 to 22:00 hours daily.",
                        "hotel_id": 74717,
                        "votes": 25
                    }
                ],
                "opted_out_of_q_and_a": 0,
                "average_response_time_text": "Subject to availability at the property"
            }
        }
    },
    "row": {
        "required": {
            "average_response_time_text": "Subject to availability at the property",
            "average_response_time_in_seconds": 2414041,
            "average_response_time": "This property usually replies within a few days",
            "success": 1,
            "q_and_a_pairs": [
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1571923294,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2019-10-23 13:04:42",
                    "question": "Is there a hand shower",
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 1489869,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 29,
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1571835882,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1598246897,
                    "asked_at": "2020-08-24 00:35:18",
                    "answer": "Yes sir, we can provide the same subject to availability at the time of arrival.",
                    "question": "Hi i have elderly parents and they would arrive in domestic flight and would be travelling on international flight . do you offer early check in around 11am?",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1598229318,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 4386257,
                    "votes": 27,
                    "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hello. Do you have swimming pool and is it available to use now? Best regards, Tatiana",
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is operational from 06:00 to 22:00 hours daily.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653844021,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-26 06:41:21",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                    "votes": 25,
                    "question_id": 25104804,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653547281,
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:11:39",
                    "votes": 24,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 1400862,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:11:39",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1569867398,
                    "naive_sentiment": -77,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question": "How do I organise a pick up from the airport when I arrive",
                    "answer": "The same can be arranged at an additional cost.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422299,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2019-09-30 18:16:38",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:26:28",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:26:28",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1555235763,
                    "naive_sentiment": -5,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 23,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 35017,
                    "question": "With out married couples are allowed or no",
                    "answer": "Yes. the guests are allowed.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1598246788,
                    "asked_at": "2019-04-14 09:56:03",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "votes": 20,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 1629646,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2019-11-18 14:16:58",
                    "naive_sentiment": -23,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1573679298,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2019-11-18 14:16:58",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hi \nPete here. I'm traveling with my teenage daughter. I'm interested in a room with 2 beds. from 12/27-12/31. \ndo you have a room like that? \nthank you",
                    "answer": "We have limited twin beds in the Superior / Deluxe city view category in the Taj Mahal Tower and Luxury Grand City view room in the Taj Mahal Palace. In case, it’s not available, we can arrange for a Hollywood twin set up, where there are 02 separate duvets placed on one king bed. Request you to kindly place a request for the same once your reservation has been processed.",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-13 21:08:18",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1574086618,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1602430840,
                    "asked_at": "2019-03-31 07:24:00",
                    "question": "Can driver have room to stay",
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, An additional room will need to be booked.",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1554017040,
                    "naive_sentiment": -11,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-11 15:40:40",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15642,
                    "votes": 17,
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-11 15:40:40",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Prepayment is possible?",
                    "answer": "Yes, prepayment via a secure payment link is possible.",
                    "asked_at": "2019-04-04 17:42:52",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1598246771,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:26:11",
                    "votes": 14,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 22290,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:26:11",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1554399772,
                    "naive_sentiment": 87,
                    "room_id": 7471707
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 4887537,
                    "votes": 13,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601449386,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-09-30 07:11:37",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2020-09-30 07:11:37",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1601449897,
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-30 07:03:06",
                    "question": "Pure vegetarian food available?",
                    "answer": "Yes sir, we can provide pure vegetarian food."
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887410,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-17 11:34:07",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Breakfast complementary....?",
                    "answer": "Dear guest, This depends on the package booked at.",
                    "question_id": 6529143,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 9,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610883247,
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:43:30",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:43:30",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Includes a pre-set meal for dinner, breakfast and pre-set meal for lunch at a pre-designated venue. The set meal will be available at the All day dining Shamiana will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked.",
                    "question": "Full board meal means",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1620361758,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-06 21:34:51",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-07 04:29:18",
                    "votes": 8,
                    "question_id": 9578648,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-07 04:29:18",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620336891,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 59
                },
                {
                    "votes": 8,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12389604,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:11:21",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625498174,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:11:21",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in which a guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "question": "Does the Superior Room Sea View King Bed option come with a stand in balcony?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584281,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-05 15:16:14"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is there bath tub available in every room?",
                    "answer": "We have walk-in showers only in the Superior and Deluxe room categories.",
                    "asked_at": "2019-09-13 06:39:25",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422273,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:11:13",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:11:13",
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1568356765,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 7,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 1282947
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-12 13:38:47",
                    "votes": 7,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 6984568,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-12 13:38:47",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": -17,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612766769,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answer": "The set meal is available at the All day dining restaurant Shamiana and will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked. ",
                    "question": "if we are booking for full board menu, how it will be served? In room or buffet menu?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613137127,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-08 06:46:09",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-19 14:49:28",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-19 14:49:28",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608285709,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 6,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 5951101,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. Due to the current pandemic situation it takes longer to have the room ready (cleaned and sanitised) after a guest checks out and hence appreciate your understanding and co-operation.",
                    "question": "Can you allow late checkout",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608389368,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-18 10:01:49",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:38:25",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:38:25",
                    "room_id": 7471721,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613510737,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 33,
                    "votes": 6,
                    "room_name": "Apollo Suite Sea View with complimentary one way Airport Transfer and daily evening cocktails at Taj Club Lounge",
                    "question_id": 7219783,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "The meals are included in the Suite Surprises package.",
                    "question": "Lunch inculcated",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831905,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-16 21:25:37",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-06 17:00:43",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-06 17:00:43",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601994612,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 51,
                    "votes": 5,
                    "question_id": 4973338,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, The room is a city facing room. We would suggest to book the Deluxe Sea view room or the Apollo Suite for panaromic views of the Gateway of India and the harbour. The Supeior Sea view rooms located on the lower floors also has a sea view.",
                    "question": "Is this room Gateway of India facing?",
                    "asked_at": "2020-10-06 14:30:12",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1602003643,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:28:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654517664,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:28:31",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25637337,
                    "votes": 4,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-06 12:14:24",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227311,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "How much it cost for airport shuttle?Thanks",
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Yes, we request you to pre-book and arrive.",
                    "question": "People coming from kamothe navi mumbai are allowed",
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-26 08:44:43",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1601449928,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-09-30 07:12:08",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-09-30 07:12:08",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601109883,
                    "naive_sentiment": 71,
                    "votes": 4,
                    "question_id": 4834302,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1622563231,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-25 09:36:39",
                    "answer": "The full board package begins with dinner on day of arrival.",
                    "question": "What is the first meal on the check-in day on full board",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621935399,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 53,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-01 16:00:31",
                    "question_id": 10319293,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 4,
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-01 16:00:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422760,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-04 13:46:58",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Bathtub is there?",
                    "answer": "The Bathtub is available only in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and the rooms in the Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Please do ensure the preference is requested for at the time of booking.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:19:20",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607089618,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:19:20",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 5705684,
                    "votes": 4
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 17:00:34",
                    "votes": 4,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5856380,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 17:00:34",
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607845617,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question": "I have a puppy.. allowed?",
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President -IHCL Seleqtions is a pet freindly hotel, in case you wish to travel with your companion.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051634,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-13 07:46:57",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624513163,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-20 21:36:48",
                    "answer": "Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out. •\tMeal service timings are as follows : Lunch: 12:30hrs to 15:00hrs & Dinner: 19:00hrs to 23:00hrs.",
                    "question": "After check in at 3:00 pm in to the hotel at what time will be full board meals for existing and other day till 11 pm check out will be served?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:39:23",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 11600510,
                    "votes": 2,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624225008,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 97,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:39:23"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Smoking rooms are available subject to availability.",
                    "question": "Hii is smoking room available",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570679,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-21 18:20:44",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:51:19",
                    "votes": 2,
                    "question_id": 16215413,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:51:19",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632248444,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584147,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-26 08:33:16",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Unmarried couples are allowed or not..??",
                    "answer": "Unmarried couple are allowed. Valid photo id proofs will be required at check-in.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:09:07",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1622017996,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:09:07",
                    "question_id": 10365533,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 2
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234556,
                    "asked_at": "2022-10-22 19:36:19",
                    "question": "Hi, do you have airport pickup service available? And the cost please?",
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 31862932,
                    "votes": 2,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1666467379,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:29:16",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:29:16",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 2,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 38128479,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-07-12 11:06:06",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1689102098,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-07-12 11:06:06",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Maximum 3 guests including children can be accommodated in one room, with one extra bed. ",
                    "question": "We stayed a few times at your wonderful hotel some years ago. We have 3 teenages now. Is it possible to put an extra bed in the room? Two double+1 bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1689159966,
                    "asked_at": "2023-07-11 19:01:38",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-02 12:48:04",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584563,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Breakfast is on a buffet basis at the All Day Dining Shamiana.",
                    "question": "I am asking if the Breakfast is ABF OR CONTINENTAL? n no one is replying.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:16:03",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 12219202,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 2,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "naive_sentiment": -75,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625230084,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:16:03"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-01 16:36:58",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351734,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Hi we are looking to book if staying in the tower can we use switch pool and facilities at the palace\nRegards jon",
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently non-operational as per government policy. If booked for the Tower you have access to the general public areas like the shopping arcade, the restaurants, etc. However the residential floors are exclusively for the guest",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 16583477,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1633106218,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:48:54",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:48:54",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Dear guest, the photo id proofs will be required. Individuals with a cough, cold, or a temperature of more than 98.6F or 37.3C will regrettably not be permitted entry into the hotel premises for the safety and security of all concerned. ",
                    "question": "I am a local can I come to stay if yes what all documents are required ?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619083361,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-14 10:24:57",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8833178,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-22 09:22:41",
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618395897,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 77,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-22 09:22:41"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:14:58",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 10019315,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621336098,
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:14:58",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354498,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-18 11:08:18",
                    "question": "What is the check in and check out time",
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.\nWe recommend to arrive by the standard timings to ensure a ready room on arrival.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-16 16:37:19",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831865,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. We recommend to arrive by the standard timings to ensure a ready room on arrival. ",
                    "question": "Hi!\nIs there any option for early check in? Like 11 am in the morning?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:37:45",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 7211237,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 73,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613493439,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:37:45"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539101,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-05 13:03:40",
                    "question": "Hie do u allow unmarried couples ?",
                    "answer": "Yes we can accomodate unmarried couples",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612530220,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:31:41",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6924533,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:31:41",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:46:49",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1609669470,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 6236868,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:46:49",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Dear guest, the room has a walk in shower and toilet.",
                    "question": "Is it facilited with bathroom",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887609,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-03 10:24:30"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613479192,
                    "naive_sentiment": 51,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:40:12",
                    "question_id": 7205334,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:40:12",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613832012,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-16 12:39:52",
                    "question": "Do you have sea view rooms with one double bed & 1 single bed to accommodate 3 people in one room?",
                    "answer": "Yes, if the booking is confirmed on triple occupancy an extra bed will be arranged for the third guest."
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830464,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-09 13:08:08",
                    "answer": "Please check the site",
                    "question": "Hi.. I need to know about the price of sea view rooms",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:14:24",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649509688,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 39,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:14:24",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 23096482,
                    "votes": 1
                },
                {
                    "votes": 1,
                    "question_id": 11695648,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:37:36",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624383852,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 39,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:37:36",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "We do have smoking rooms. Kindly place a request when processing the booking. We have french windows that open into a balcony that you can comfortably stand in.",
                    "question": "Do you have smoking room and do you have balcony or room with windows that open please let me no thank you",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624513056,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-22 17:44:12"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712061,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-15 09:05:59",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "is breakfast complimentary",
                    "answer": "Depending on the package booked.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:21:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15971845,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631696759,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 33,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:21:01"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-01 13:52:15",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-01 13:52:15",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612034896,
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "question_id": 6801321,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly check the inclusion details of the package selected.",
                    "question": "In this package of 5738/- does it include breakfast ?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612187535,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-30 19:28:16",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:34:10",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:34:10",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610968005,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 19,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 6551644,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "Yes we do have limited twin rooms available in this category.",
                    "question": "Can i get in this room twine bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831650,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-18 11:06:45",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624528794,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-20 21:18:27",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Half board is breakfast and one major set meal (dinner or lunch) while full board is set meal dinner on the arrival date, buffet breakfast and set lunch on the next day.",
                    "question": "What is meant by half board and full board meal?",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624223907,
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 09:59:54",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 11599584,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 09:59:54",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:12:38",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:12:38",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1572819117,
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 1553282,
                    "question": "Is there a spa in the room?",
                    "answer": "The Spa services are currently non-operational.",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-03 22:11:57",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422358,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:12:55",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 23231579,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649788346,
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:12:55",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830375,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-12 18:32:26",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "You can book the Superior Sea view (closer view of the Gateway of India, the Dleuxe Sea view or the Apollo Suite.",
                    "question": "Hi, I plan to stay on 7/5/22 for a night. Which room do I book to get a clear view of the Arabian Sea and India Gate",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:16:04",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 22815151,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:16:04",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1648886838,
                    "naive_sentiment": -7,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room.  Two rooms will need to be booked. Please check the charges online.",
                    "question": "We are family with 5 adults and 1 kid (7years). 17-22 April / Provide price for ocean facing room with breakfast.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830564,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-02 08:07:18",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613383863,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:37:01",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7173544,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:37:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831821,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-15 10:11:03",
                    "answer": "Please do check for the all meal inclusive package.",
                    "question": "Can breakfast & dinner be provided in package.?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hi, which floors will be the superior room sea view located.?",
                    "answer": "3rd-10th floor of the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai.",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-19 19:25:03",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831948,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:39:08",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7297748,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:39:08",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613762703,
                    "naive_sentiment": -25,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708
                },
                {
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 18951407,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:18:08",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639054167,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:18:08",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "hi do you tub bath or bath tub in all the rooms ??",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138688,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-09 12:49:27"
                },
                {
                    "question": "bath tub available and smoking room in this category",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624513063,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-21 16:27:36",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:37:43",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:37:43",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624292856,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 11636061
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 17105953,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -39,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634328873,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-16 13:08:16",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-16 13:08:16",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1634389696,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-15 20:14:33",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "how can we book room for day use",
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly."
                },
                {
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 24583876,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 13:00:22",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652604988,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 13:00:22",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "For a triple do you provide a bed for the third person? I see only 1 King size bed. Is there a sofa cum bed or any other arrangement for third person?",
                    "answer": "If the booking has been processed on triple occupancy an extra bed will be provided for the third guest.",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-15 08:56:28",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792422,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-01 12:56:36",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7547916,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614580902,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-01 12:56:36",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614603396,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-01 06:41:42",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Please select the Superior Sea view , Deluxe Sea view room or Apollo Suite for a  Sea view room.",
                    "question": "is this room  Sea facing?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Bath tub is there",
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite or in the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912601,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-27 06:44:53",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 8318597,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:23:21",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616827493,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:23:21"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-01 13:51:43",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611755274,
                    "naive_sentiment": -59,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "question_id": 6737462,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-01 13:51:43",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is there a bath tub in the bathroom?",
                    "answer": "The Superior City view room only has a walk in shower.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612187503,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-27 13:47:54"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:44:20",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614435215,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "question_id": 7502812,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:44:20",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "We can confirm an early check-in at 08:00 hrs at an addiitonal half day's charge. Arrival prior to 08:00 hrs you will have to pre-book your room from the previous night.",
                    "question": "my flight will arrive early morning, can i check in early or do I need to book for the previous day?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951860,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-27 14:13:35"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 8203661,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:28:12",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616491256,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:28:12",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. ",
                    "question": "is the pool functional",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-23 09:20:56",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912892,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-09 13:45:27",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-09 13:45:27",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610138432,
                    "naive_sentiment": -73,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "question_id": 6355339,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question": "Is the swimming pool working?",
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice as per government guidelines.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610199927,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-08 20:40:32",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "The Apollo Suite is a One bedroom Sea view Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "Apollo suits sea view is in taj mahal palace..!???",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584462,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 08:30:43",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:14:22",
                    "room_id": 7471721,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625301043,
                    "naive_sentiment": -75,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "room_name": "Apollo Suite Sea View with complimentary one way Airport Transfer and daily evening cocktails at Taj Club Lounge",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12258019,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:14:22",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-06 08:34:40",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1685863723,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 37178258,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-06 08:34:40",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hi,\nI’m looking to book for 4 nights during Easter. My flight arrives in Mumbai at 8am. Is there a possibility of getting an early check in please?",
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686040480,
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-04 07:28:43"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:20:33",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8334683,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:20:33",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616872365,
                    "naive_sentiment": 99,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, the rates offered are the best applicable rates.",
                    "question": "price kam karo not affordable please",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912433,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-27 19:12:45",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "We can offer interconnecting rooms, subject to availability on arrival",
                    "question": "Do u provide connected rooms",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1692251805,
                    "asked_at": "2023-08-12 08:35:13",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 38933227,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-08-17 05:56:45",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1691829313,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 97,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-08-17 05:56:45"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:33:56",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:33:56",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638944954,
                    "naive_sentiment": 97,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 18912085,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "Please advise if you will be staying or coming directly to the hotel.",
                    "question": "how much price veg brackfast, Lunch and dinner",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952436,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-08 06:29:14",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-06 08:38:01",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 37223244,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-06 08:38:01",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1686010541,
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question": "do the rooms have balconies?",
                    "answer": "The room category have balcony with space to stand",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686040681,
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-06 00:15:41",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351780,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-03 19:47:27",
                    "answer": "The Halfboard package includes breakfast and one major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival or lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "question": "hi, all rooms show half board as lunch and breakfast but I want dinner and breakfast. will this be upgraded or adjusted on my check in?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:49:40",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 16656836,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1633290447,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:49:40"
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13058832,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626540823,
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-20 14:02:46",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-20 14:02:46",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626789766,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-17 16:53:43",
                    "answer": "Full board includes breakfast and two major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "question": "What does full board meal include"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-02 05:22:34",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638274936,
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-02 05:22:34",
                    "question_id": 18686608,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638422554,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-30 12:22:16",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "The half board package includes breakfast and onemajor set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival or lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "question": "Half board means ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "The hotel offes a mix of European and Indian elegance, which is the architecture and design of the hotel and rooms.",
                    "question": "room offer a mix of European and Indian elegance\n means...???",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 07:35:50",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584530,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:15:30",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:15:30",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625297750,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 12256223,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "answer": "The Full board package includes breakfast and two major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "question": "What’s means full board meal",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584378,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 17:22:24",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:12:58",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12281710,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:12:58",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625332944,
                    "naive_sentiment": 93
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-22 06:10:45",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-22 06:10:45",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1682069256,
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 36112455,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "We can offer twin bedded room, subject to availability. Suite category includes complimentary one way airport transfer.",
                    "question": "Hello, can you swap a King Bed to 2 Twin Beds? \n\nDo you offer complimentary airport transfer? We are 6 Adults, and will visit for a week.\n\nThanks.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1682143845,
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-21 09:27:36",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:49:00",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25291403,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653904805,
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:49:00",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654274940,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 10:00:05",
                    "answer": "The same will be subject to availability on arrival.",
                    "question": "How can I chose the floor number ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "We can offer interconnecting with one room City view and second room sea view, subject to availability on arrival",
                    "question": "I'm travelling with my family (2 x adults and 2 x teenage children) arriving 8/12 and departing 11/12. Are you able to do interconnecting twin and double rooms. Can these be confirmed at the time of booking?\n",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1700032403,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2023-11-13 04:22:05",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-11-15 07:13:23",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-11-15 07:13:23",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1699849325,
                    "naive_sentiment": 89,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 40903587,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 6092843,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1609044915,
                    "naive_sentiment": 89,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:33:47",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:33:47",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-27 04:55:15",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831627,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "In the Deluxe and Superior category we have interconnecting room sets that are subject to availability, with one being a sea view & the other a city view room.",
                    "question": "We are a family of 5 including a child of 12 yrs, kindly confirm if you  have interconnecting see facing rooms?"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:04:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 32370574,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1667973188,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:04:01",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229441,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-11-09 05:53:08",
                    "question": "How far from int’l airport?\nDo you have shuttle service airport pick up?",
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER CAR PER WAY):  (Rates are subject to change)\n\nOption I- Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n \nOption II- SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in 1room. As there are 5 guests travelling, we would recommend 2rooms to be reserved.",
                    "question": "we are 5 members including 3 children's we need one room",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637561594,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-19 14:38:20",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-22 06:13:14",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-22 06:13:14",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1637332700,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18352013
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend 2 rooms to be reserved. You can book one city one sea in the Superior or Deluxe category, as we have ltd interconnecting sets",
                    "question": "Hello, I want to plan a staycation and we are family of 4 (kids - 11,14 yrs) is it possible to accomodate extra bed. And what charge for extra bed",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627231020,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-24 09:22:14",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 13415759,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:37:00",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627118534,
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:37:00"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:12:12",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 12593667,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:12:12",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625785757,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question": "ARRIVING 0300 ON 20TH AND DEPARTING ON 0800 AM ON 21ST \nSO HOW MANY DAYS HAS TO BE BOOKED ? AFTER LONG FLIGHT  I MUST GET ROOM WHEN ARRIVED NOT AT 1500 HRS \nPLEASE CLARIFY",
                    "answer": "Kindly do advise where you will be travelling from. The booking will need to be processed from the 19-20th to ensure a ready room on arrival.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088332,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-08 23:09:17",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686718633,
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-10 07:07:34",
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST",
                    "question": "what will be the charge to the airport t2",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-14 04:57:13",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1686380854,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-14 04:57:13",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 37324874,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:14:03",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1662023733,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 30092625,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:14:03",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "question": "Hi is there an airport shuttle or are you close to the metro",
                    "asked_at": "2022-09-01 09:15:33",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233643,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-03 18:45:49",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227273,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Airport pickup charge?",
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654281949,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:27:53",
                    "question_id": 25513077,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:27:53",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-19 05:28:14",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570584,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Yes unmarried couples are allowed. Valid photo id proofs will be required at check-in.",
                    "question": "unmarried couples are allowed..?",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632029294,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:49:44",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 16112486,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:49:44",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-18 17:28:40",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465089,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Full board includes which meals ?? High tea and lounge access included ??",
                    "answer": "The full board includes breakfast and two major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out. High tea will be at an additional charge. Lounge is non-ope",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:11:29",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629307720,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:11:29",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14810625,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2022-12-29 19:20:17",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228597,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "if i stay in tajmahal tower can i attend tajmahal palace resturant",
                    "answer": "Yes you can",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:49:57",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 33438024,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "naive_sentiment": 81,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1672341617,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:49:57"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Yes you can ",
                    "question": "if i stay in tajmahal tower can i visit resturant shamiana",
                    "asked_at": "2022-12-29 19:21:14",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228575,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:49:35",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:49:35",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1672341674,
                    "naive_sentiment": 81,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 33438039,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hello sir\nI'm married couples and one baby girl Age 10 old  to family room Available and lunch and Dinner extra pay ya  including for Booking",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. ",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040056,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-06 15:18:37",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:07:36",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628263117,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 79,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14162541,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:07:36",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:10:44",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:10:44",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625501203,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 79,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 12392599,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. ",
                    "question": "If I book with half board a superior room sea facing - will dinner be included for my kids aged 5 and 10",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584244,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-05 16:06:43",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-05 10:15:55",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539129,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly check the rates on the site",
                    "question": "One day package with food",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6921580,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612520155,
                    "naive_sentiment": 79,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:32:09",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:32:09",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 46563953,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1722509962,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2024-08-05 08:49:44",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2024-08-05 08:49:44",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2024-08-01 10:59:22",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1722847784,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Are there rooms with an ocean view ?",
                    "answer": "We have sea view option in all room categories at Taj Mahal Tower"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Yes. Kindly request for the same when processing the booking.",
                    "question": "Hi, do you have smoking rooms available?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088493,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-07 18:44:58",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:14:53",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 12522770,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:14:53",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625683498,
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "The smae will be at an addittional charge. Kindly do request the same directly from the booking.",
                    "question": "Do u have a facilities for airport drop ?",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613137168,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-10 15:00:56",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7051694,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-12 13:39:28",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612969256,
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-12 13:39:28"
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15097147,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629832613,
                    "naive_sentiment": 73,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:55:42",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:55:42",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899742,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-24 19:16:53",
                    "question": "unmarried couple allow this hotel",
                    "answer": "Yes unmarried couples are allowed. A valid photo id proofs will be required per guest at the time of check-in."
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5849973,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 16:58:23",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607802015,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 73,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 16:58:23",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "its my dream stay 1 day at Taj hotel.but the check in timing and checkout timing are 20th december  night 11pm to 21st december 11.pm .  sea facing",
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. For a late check-out at 23:00 hrs the room wil need booked till the 22nd December.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051503,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-12 19:40:15"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:53:48",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "naive_sentiment": 71,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629711301,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:53:48",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15021249,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-23 09:35:01",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899628,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "I want room for 24 hrs price ??",
                    "answer": "Kindly view the rates online. Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kindly do refer to the web site for the details for the same.",
                    "question": "kindly let us know your charges for breakfast + dinner on 30/07 and 31/07/2021 along with accomodation charges for superior sea view room for 2 pax",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626278817,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-12 16:02:34",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-14 16:06:57",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-14 16:06:57",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626105754,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 71,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 12777378,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229471,
                    "asked_at": "2022-11-10 14:32:46",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "You can leave the bags with the bell desk till the check in",
                    "question": "Does the hotel offers a clock room facility  to keep the baggage for early arrival guests ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:04:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 32411423,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1668090766,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:04:31"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:06:12",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:06:12",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653039770,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 24830490,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. We recommend to adhere by the standard timings.",
                    "question": "How many hours check out time",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653843972,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-20 09:42:50",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:43:30",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 17728534,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1635798368,
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:43:30",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907410,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-01 20:26:08",
                    "question": "Do you have shuttle service from Mumbai Airport",
                    "answer": "The airport transfer can be arranged at charge. Kindly do write to us directly from the messaging option on your booking.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-09 11:12:23",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 8690402,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-09 11:12:23",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1617966603,
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question": "Pool access available?",
                    "answer": "In light of the current situation, we have implemented enhanced precautionary hygiene measures across our hotel. As per government advisories, certain services, including Swimming Pool are non-operational.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1617966743,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-09 11:10:03",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-10 09:24:25",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233780,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. ",
                    "question": "What is checking in and out time",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:16:20",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 29081704,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660123465,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:16:20"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227295,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-06 07:24:10",
                    "question": "What is the Check in time",
                    "answer": "Kindly note the standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. ",
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654500250,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:28:15",
                    "question_id": 25624226,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:28:15",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 21137316,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644759396,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:25:45",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:25:45",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827145,
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-13 13:36:36",
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "question": "Are check out time flexible ?"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:07:07",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14146430,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:07:07",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628243040,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question": "What is the policy for children",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. Children above 12 years are considered as adults. Children up to 12 years of age will be entitled to a free stay in the existing bedding on room only basis. ",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040027,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-06 09:44:00",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "question": "check in time?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176279,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-03 06:33:40",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13962500,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:11:19",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627972420,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:11:19"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621840388,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-22 14:45:53",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Timing check in check out",
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "question_id": 10197596,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621694753,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-24 07:13:08",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-24 07:13:08",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "question": "check in time & check out time",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422639,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-06 17:32:01",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 5740522,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:17:19",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607275921,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:17:19"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:56",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25257175,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:56",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653839230,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answer": "Please check the site for the available tarrifs.",
                    "question": "Breakfast and dinner with room tariff",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-29 15:47:10",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653844076,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952369,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-03 08:22:19",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. One Child up to 12 years of age will be entitled to a free stay in the existing bedding on room only basis. ",
                    "question": "Hi, I am visiting 31st March and 15th April. I would like to book 2 rooms with 3 occupants each, is it possible to add an extra kids bed in each room?",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638519739,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:32:49",
                    "question_id": 18771542,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:32:49",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051451,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-12 13:27:08",
                    "question": "i want a room but the check in timing and chect oot timing is from 11.pm to 11.pm\nfor 1 day  seaview in taj",
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.  For the late check-out at 23:00 hrs an additional full day's charge will be applicable.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607779628,
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 16:57:31",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5844398,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 16:57:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-24 12:29:39",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-24 12:29:39",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1599990695,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 4652438,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question": "Are unmarried couples allowed for accommodation",
                    "answer": "Yes we can accomodate unmarried couples",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1603542579,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-13 09:51:35",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 14270561,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:08:18",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628444592,
                    "naive_sentiment": 63,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:08:18",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "what's the difference between superior room and deluxe room?",
                    "answer": "Superior rooms are located between the 3rd-10th floor while Deluxe rooms are located between the 11-19th floor.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040098,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-08 17:43:12"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is outside alcohol allowed?",
                    "answer": "Yes int he room only.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040039,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-06 12:11:58",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:07:19",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14153465,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:07:19",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628251918,
                    "naive_sentiment": 61,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "hii. can we accomadate an extra person in our room since my mother will be accompanying us. 3 adults and 1 child.",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests in one room including children.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831973,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-18 13:06:24",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:39:33",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:39:33",
                    "naive_sentiment": 61,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613653584,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7263220
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-22 09:23:20",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-22 09:23:20",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618551020,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 59,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8889225,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, Unmarried couple's are allowed as long as the valid photo id proofs are shared.",
                    "question": "Unmarried  couples  (lover's) are allowed or not?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619083400,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-16 05:30:20",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is swimming pool working?",
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently non-operational.",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-11 15:25:34",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613137192,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 7080228,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-12 13:39:52",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613057134,
                    "naive_sentiment": 59,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-12 13:39:52"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is there any charge for swimming pool",
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently non-operational.",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-01 05:28:59",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422327,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 1534037,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:12:07",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1572586139,
                    "naive_sentiment": 59,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:12:07"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1697515523,
                    "asked_at": "2023-09-19 23:21:32",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "What are the timing for breakfast and dinner?",
                    "answer": "Daily breakfast will be served between 7:00 hrs. to 10:30hrs at a pre-designated dining venue\n• Meal service timings are mentioned as below:\no Lunch: 12:30hrs to 15:00hrs\no Dinner: 19:00hrs to 23:30hrs",
                    "question_id": 39823902,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "naive_sentiment": 57,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1695165692,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-10-17 04:05:23",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-10-17 04:05:23",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": 57,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621803181,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-24 07:13:51",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 10253496,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-24 07:13:51",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621840431,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-23 20:53:01",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests in total in a room including children.",
                    "question": "How many persons can accommodate in a room??"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 12:59:25",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 24646429,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 12:59:25",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 55,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652711817,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answer": "We can arrnage for the interconnecting set in the Superior and Deluxe category with one room being a sea view adn the other a city view. However the rooms are limited. The City view room room will be a twin bedded room.",
                    "question": "We want two rooms with connected door and separately bed",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-16 14:36:57",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792365,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827021,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-13 09:59:09",
                    "question": "Hello,  as we have the room with dinner option, which restaurants should be available for us? What will be the dinner options?",
                    "answer": "The breakfast and one major set meal at a pre-designated venue will be at the All day dining restaurant the Shamiana.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:23:41",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 21129741,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "naive_sentiment": 55,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644746349,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:23:41"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633854631,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-09 17:26:48",
                    "answer": "In light of the current situation, we have implemented enhanced precautionary hygiene measures across our hotel. As per government advisories, certain services, likeSwimming Pool, is non-operational.",
                    "question": "Is swimming pool operational?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-10 08:30:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1633800408,
                    "naive_sentiment": 53,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-10 08:30:31",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 16876687,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-23 07:05:14",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "naive_sentiment": 53,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621364661,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-23 07:05:14",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 10038976,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621753514,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-18 19:04:21",
                    "question": "Cant we decorate the room for birthday celebration",
                    "answer": "The same can be aanged at charge. Kindly do write to us directly from the booking confirmation. ",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465188,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-20 10:37:32",
                    "question": "Planning to book for 21-22 aug, 2 rooms 4 adults . Early check in possible ??",
                    "answer": "Subject to room availability. Kindly place the request directly from your room booking.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:13:08",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629455852,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:13:08",
                    "question_id": 14894081,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:11:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14049202,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628090807,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:11:01",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176261,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-04 15:26:47",
                    "question": "Hi m planing to visit the Taj Mahal palace with my mom my sis me my wife & my 8 yrs old son.what kind of room would u suggest me.\nAlso the room rate.",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. ",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627230943,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-24 17:08:05",
                    "question": "What are best offers for family of four for one day including all meals. We can stay in one room also",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. ",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:35:43",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627146485,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:35:43",
                    "question_id": 13436077,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-19 15:23:34",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626789742,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "As per government advisories, certain services, including Swimming Pool, may be non-operational. The health and safety of our guests and associates is our utmost priority and we look forward to welcoming you at the hotel.",
                    "question": "Hi is the pool functional?",
                    "question_id": 13159878,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626708214,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-20 14:02:22",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-20 14:02:22",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. ",
                    "question": "Can 4 guests occupy a single room",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626363904,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-15 15:01:34",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12950563,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-15 15:45:04",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626361294,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-15 15:45:04"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Does Breakfast lunch and dinner is applicable for all 3 peoples.",
                    "answer": "If the booking is made on triple occupancy on the package that includes Breakfast lunch and dinner then the meals are applicable for all three guests.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1617773305,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-04 12:31:12",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-07 05:28:25",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-07 05:28:25",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1617539472,
                    "naive_sentiment": 47,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 8543925,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627231055,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-23 11:12:54",
                    "answer": "Kindly check the available packages on the site",
                    "question": "Would like to stay in the palace wing of this iconic hotel on my first ever trip to Mumbai from 30th July to 1st August.Please help .",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:37:35",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 13372145,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627038774,
                    "naive_sentiment": 45,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:37:35"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2020-11-04 19:16:09",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1604412659,
                    "naive_sentiment": 45,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-11-04 19:16:09",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5315034,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1604517369,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-03 14:10:59",
                    "answer": "Kindly do request for a smoking room.",
                    "question": "Is smoking allowed in the balcony?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:02:19",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 32994805,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1670323394,
                    "naive_sentiment": 43,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:02:19",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229339,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-12-06 10:43:14",
                    "question": "I will be travelling to India with my husband, 10 month baby and currently pregnant. Will I be able to check in earlier around 1pm?",
                    "answer": "The same can be confirmed, subject to availability, on arrival",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Thank you for your interest. We needed some additional details regarding your requirement to be able to respond to your query.   ",
                    "question": "Is it the collest hotle of mumbai?",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1600436668,
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-18 13:31:29",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-09-18 13:44:28",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 4723892,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-09-18 13:44:28",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1600435889,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 43
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:13:14",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628769238,
                    "naive_sentiment": 41,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:13:14",
                    "question_id": 14486040,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040394,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-12 11:53:58",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly refer to the web site for applicable rates.",
                    "question": "If I want to include Dinner also during my stay for 3 nights then what would be charges total",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Superior Room City view and Deluxe room city view have twin bedded room, subject to availability",
                    "question": "Do you provide Twin rooms? I am looking at booking a hotel in Mumbai for x6 adults (males) but can’t seem to find any options to book twin rooms?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1681360362,
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-12 23:42:02",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 35903187,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-13 04:32:42",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1681342922,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 39,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-13 04:32:42"
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 18:03:22",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275138,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. Children above 12 years are considered as adults. ",
                    "question": "Hello ,\n\nWe are a family of 4 person and i would like to get 1 room,is that possible? 2 adult 2 teenagers.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:52:18",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25314364,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653933802,
                    "naive_sentiment": 37,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:52:18"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hi. we are family of 4, 2 adults and 2 k8ds age 9 and 14 yrs. we want half board package, what booking option should we take",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. Children above 12 years are considered as adults. ",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088479,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-08 15:59:42",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:14:39",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:14:39",
                    "naive_sentiment": 37,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625759982,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 12570867
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 16:56:22",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607883083,
                    "naive_sentiment": 33,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 16:56:22",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5866078,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051382,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-13 18:11:23",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is there any charges for jacuzzi????",
                    "answer": "Kindly note the room category booked only has a walk-in shower.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "question": "we are  coming from gulf . planning to stay here for one day.Can we call relatives to meet us .If yes how many members can meet and what is the time .",
                    "answer": "Maximum of 4 guests can meeat in a room and the visitor timings are from 09:00-20:00 hrs. Incase there are more guests you can meet them in one of the restaurants with a prior table reservation.",
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-01 19:30:25",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275241,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:54:01",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:54:01",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654111825,
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25419978
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14688392,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629120336,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:09:46",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:09:46",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629464986,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-16 13:25:36",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly write to us from the message option on your booking for the Celebrations menu.",
                    "question": "It’s my husbands birthday on the 24th .., can you do something special for him"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12782524,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-14 16:07:24",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626111182,
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-14 16:07:24",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in whicha  guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "question": "Hi, \nDo I get a balcony in my room?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626278844,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-12 17:33:02"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621009238,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-14 15:01:14",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Hi\nWhat do you mean by FULL BOARD included?",
                    "answer": "Full board would mean the room rate is inclusive of all meals (breakfast, lunch and dinner)",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-14 16:20:38",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 9864650,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621004474,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-14 16:20:38"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-23 07:04:27",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-23 07:04:27",
                    "naive_sentiment": 29,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621629191,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 10172802,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question": "Hi .Is the pool and spa operational or its closed due to Covid.Also If I book a Full board meal,Is it on Al Al a Carte or it is vast spread buffet.",
                    "answer": "TH ehotel is operational as per gvernment restrictions. The Full board meals is a set meal ofered at the All Day dining restaurant Shamiana.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621753467,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-21 20:33:11",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422598,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-07 03:26:22",
                    "answer": "The meal in the package that includes meals is served at a pre-designated dining venue. If the package includes hotel credit then that credit can be used against In room dining food orders.",
                    "question": "If we book for an inclusive dinner will it be served in the room ?",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607311582,
                    "naive_sentiment": 29,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:16:38",
                    "question_id": 5748024,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:16:38",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-03-05 07:20:37",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-03-05 07:20:37",
                    "naive_sentiment": 29,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1583089763,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 2729807,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question": "I only want dinner can i book a table",
                    "answer": "We would request you to kindly contact Our Food & Beverages team on the hotel contact number mentioned on the Taj hotel contact details so that they can assist you with the applicable options. ",
                    "asked_at": "2020-03-01 19:09:23",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1583392837,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907329,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-22 16:22:08",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Hi I want to stay at your Hotel if I brings an other person till date not final then what is you extra Bed Charges",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. The third occupant would be charged INR. 3000+18% taxes.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:42:09",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634919728,
                    "naive_sentiment": 25,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:42:09",
                    "question_id": 17360389,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:46:58",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 16417905,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632737465,
                    "naive_sentiment": 25,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:46:58",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351618,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-27 10:11:05",
                    "answer": "The Superior Sea view rooms are located between the 3rd-10th floors while the Deluxe Sea view rooms are located between the 11th-19th floors. They both have Sea view. The higher the floors the more birds eye view of the Gateway Of India is viewable.",
                    "question": "Hi, will the Deluxe and Superior sea view rooms both have a view of the ocean and the Gateway? What is the difference between these two rooms?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 26864057,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1656589769,
                    "naive_sentiment": 23,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:27:01",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:27:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234421,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-30 11:49:29",
                    "answer": "The hotel has the options of smoking & non-smoking accommodation",
                    "question": "Smoking arrangements"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138669,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-08 12:48:06",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "We can note the request for the early check-in however we are unable to confirm the same. Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. ",
                    "question": "We want to check in before time 12 pm on 17 December is it possible",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638967686,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 23,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:17:49",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18920348,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:17:49",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:22:41",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15952945,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:22:41",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631646307,
                    "naive_sentiment": 23,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question": "Hii i have booked room, according to my flight time i will reach around 9:30. Can we do early check in",
                    "answer": "Subject to availability. Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. In case the room is not ready  you can leave your baggage at the Bell Desk and check in later.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712161,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-14 19:05:07",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1682143757,
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-21 23:23:48",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "hi could we request an extra bed for 3rd adult",
                    "answer": "We can arrange for an extra bed at INR 3000+taxes per night",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-22 06:09:17",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1682119428,
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-22 06:09:17",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 36127910,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830509,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-03 19:00:53",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Do you have any options that can accommodate 4 guests in a room?",
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. Two rooms will need to be booked.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:15:09",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 22872877,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649012453,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:15:09"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Please place the request directly on your booking chat service.",
                    "question": "i want inter connected room",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351132,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-26 11:35:02",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:38:52",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 16383495,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:38:52",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632656102,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 21
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, if you do select the set meal package with all meals, the same is at the All day dining restaurant Shamiana and will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per guest booked. ",
                    "question": "Is sea lounge access included in the all meal package?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-20 17:27:38",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619083553,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-22 09:25:53",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 9024565,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-22 09:25:53",
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618939658,
                    "naive_sentiment": 21
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:33:26",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 19,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638856271,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:33:26",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18881299,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952406,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-07 05:51:11",
                    "answer": "We can offer an early check in at 08:00 am at additional half day charge. Kindly advise in case you wish to avail the same.",
                    "question": "Dear sir / Madam\nMy name is Virendra Kewadkar from Aurangabad,\nthere is no any Flexible time for check in at 8.00 in the morning.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227913,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-17 16:10:17",
                    "question": "Is own liquor bottles allowed?",
                    "answer": "You can carry one liquor bottle for consumption in the room",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:38:33",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1655482217,
                    "naive_sentiment": 17,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:38:33",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 26201721,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627487273,
                    "naive_sentiment": 17,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:06:00",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13656833,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:06:00",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-28 15:47:53",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905960,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "The set meal at Shamiana will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked. ",
                    "question": "Half Board includes breakfast and dinner at any restaurant of your choice or ?"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "hi, is there complimentary breakfast",
                    "answer": "Depends on the package booked",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1630415541,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-28 17:03:47",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15265331,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-31 13:12:21",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630170227,
                    "naive_sentiment": 15,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-31 13:12:21"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628328395,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-07 07:39:49",
                    "question": "is vaccine certification is compulsory? I m planning to book for 2 tomorrow",
                    "answer": "\n\nDear Sir,\n \nGreetings from the Taj.\n\n\n\nFurther to the below email, vaccination certificate is not compulsory.  You can fill the health declaration form on arrival.\n\nRegards,\n\nKrishin\nReservations",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14192352,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628321989,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 15,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-07 09:26:35",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-07 09:26:35",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 13767433,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:05:09",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627658605,
                    "naive_sentiment": 15,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:05:09",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Individuals with a cough, cold, or a temperature of more than 98.6F or 37.3C will regrettably not be permitted entry into the hotel premises for the safety and security of all concerned. ",
                    "question": "is there any conditions for 60 above bcz of ds covid situation",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-30 15:23:25",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905909,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637561616,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-21 14:23:19",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is balcony attached to every rooms?",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in which a guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 18410162,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1637504599,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-22 06:13:36",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-22 06:13:36",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712094,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-15 05:17:54",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in which a guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "question": "does it have a standing balcony?",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631683074,
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:21:34",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15967274,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:21:34",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 13770414,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627662218,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:04:02",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:04:02",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905842,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-30 16:23:38",
                    "answer": "Please check the available packages on the site.",
                    "question": "include dinner"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351382,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-27 01:17:48",
                    "answer": "The pool service is currently non-operational. The health and safety of our guests and associates is our utmost priority and we look forward to welcoming you at the hotel. Towels are provided in the room.",
                    "question": "For pool and towel we have to give additional charge \nOr it is in the price of room only",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:43:02",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632705468,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 11,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:43:02",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 16409236,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627230917,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-25 11:05:09",
                    "answer": "Kindly check the package booked",
                    "question": "What food included for this booking",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:35:17",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13466840,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627211109,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 11,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:35:17"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-18 11:01:35",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-18 11:01:35",
                    "naive_sentiment": 9,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631741614,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 15999192,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question": "Do you accept HDFC Bank Diners Credit Card",
                    "answer": "We accept credit cards.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631962895,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-15 21:33:34",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "All meal charges pl",
                    "answer": "Please do check the webite for details fo the same.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584394,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 12:54:21",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:13:14",
                    "naive_sentiment": 9,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625316861,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12268875,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:13:14",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 40378509,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-10-17 04:08:15",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1697474654,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-10-17 04:08:15",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hello, we have two children and my husband and I would all like to be in the same room. Is this possible as it’s saying we need 2 separate rooms?",
                    "answer": "As per hotel policy, we can accommodate maximum 3 guests in a room (including children). In event of 4 guests, 2 rooms must be booked.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1697515695,
                    "asked_at": "2023-10-16 16:44:14",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "hi how do we book honeymoon suite",
                    "answer": "Please refere to the rates available online. Once booked we can share the various celebrations packages available.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1641387060,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-05 12:29:23",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-01-05 12:51:00",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 19717307,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-01-05 12:51:00",
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641385763,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:58:30",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639590508,
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 19137456,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:58:30",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Please check the rate description it will advise whats included in the package.",
                    "question": "food is included in the stay price or not",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599110,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-15 17:48:28",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:57:32",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 19033110,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639314459,
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:57:32",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599052,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-12 13:07:39",
                    "question": "Hi\nBreakfast included in this rate ?",
                    "answer": "Please check the rate description.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599040,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-10 19:03:35",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "can driver stay there ?",
                    "answer": "A seperate room will need to be booked as available online.",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18989388,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639163015,
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:57:20",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:57:20",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14863106,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:11:57",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629393556,
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:11:57",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Please refer to the online rates fot the same",
                    "question": "We want breakfast and Dinner package too",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465117,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-19 17:19:16",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275166,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 19:48:03",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "There are showr blinds which can be lowered.",
                    "question": "I have noticed from the room picture that the shower room is exposed, is there any curtains or a way to cover it?",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653940083,
                    "naive_sentiment": 5,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:52:46",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25320098,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:52:46",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620544903,
                    "naive_sentiment": 5,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:15:53",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 9653772,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:15:53",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354553,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-09 07:21:43",
                    "answer": "Yes we hvae Jain food available. While the booking is being processed please share your preference for Jain food.",
                    "question": "if we book with full board, is thier jain food avaible"
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 7586849,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614695678,
                    "naive_sentiment": 5,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:44:59",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:44:59",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951899,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-02 14:34:38",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "The GST depends on your room rate.",
                    "question": "Hi this amount included GSt"
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 23105959,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649526165,
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:14:01",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:14:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830441,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-09 17:42:45",
                    "answer": "Yes fully vaccinated guests  or guests with RTPCR of 48 hours prior will be accepted.",
                    "question": "Are only vaccinated travelers from COVID-19 allowed to stay at the hotel?"
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625763740,
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:13:47",
                    "question_id": 12574191,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:13:47",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088427,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-08 17:02:20",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests in a room including children. Children above 12 are considered as adults. If the booking is processed on triple occupancy basis it will include the extra bed and meals as per the package booked.",
                    "question": "if i take a half board package and take an additional bed at rs 3000 for my 14 year old kid, will she be included in half board package?"
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 10319376,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621935490,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:08:39",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:08:39",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584119,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-25 09:38:10",
                    "answer": "The meal is only inclusive for the adults booked. There is a child supplement charge applicable fo rhte meals of the child.",
                    "question": "Does one have to pay extra charges for child meal even if the plan opted is full board for 2 adults and 1 kid"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is brekfast including this prices?",
                    "answer": "Please check the inclusions in your package.",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-03 07:47:02",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830521,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 22848250,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:15:21",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1648972022,
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:15:21"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:47:19",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:47:19",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632908338,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 16496414,
                    "answer": "Depends on the package selected.",
                    "question": "is lunch, dinner and BF included?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351639,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-29 09:38:58",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14888180,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:12:41",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629446397,
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:12:41",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is the dinner included in package a buffet or set menu?",
                    "answer": "Please refere to the inclusions of the package booked. If booked a package inclsuive of set meals. The set meal at Shamiana will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465161,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-20 07:59:57"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Are there any new Covid-19 norms regarding stays at hotels and restaurants. Also which floor does the deluxe sea view room starts.",
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly as the chat space is limited. Deluxe rooms are located between the 11-19th floor.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040370,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-12 10:30:00",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14481962,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:12:50",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628764200,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:12:50"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Yes. Please ensure you mention the preference for Jain food in your reservation.",
                    "question": "is Jain food available?",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422624,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-06 17:34:02",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5740564,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:17:04",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607276042,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:17:04"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 19178572,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:58:05",
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "naive_sentiment": -1,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639717909,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:58:05",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Each hotel has a different policy.",
                    "question": "Why it is confined to only one starter, main course and one desert in full board  Rest of the properties have a buffet in one of their restaurant",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599085,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-17 05:11:49"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is there bathtub in sea view room?",
                    "answer": "Apollo Suite category only have bathtub",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1683268973,
                    "asked_at": "2023-05-04 09:08:38",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-05-05 06:42:53",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-05-05 06:42:53",
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1683191318,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 36438930
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-02 07:07:23",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 35626761,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1680345929,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-02 07:07:23",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1680419243,
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-01 10:45:29",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "The room has a bathroom with toilet and shower cubicle",
                    "question": "Hi, just wanted to confirm that the bathroom\nwith this room is not shared? In the booking overview, it is says that it is a room with shared bathroom.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "unmarried couples allowed?",
                    "answer": "Yes, both guests will need to carry valid photo id proof.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088211,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-10 15:58:45",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:10:11",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:10:11",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625932725,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12673386
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 7156064,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:40:48",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613318902,
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:40:48",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "for extra person there is any charges",
                    "answer": "Kindly process the booking on triple occupancy if three guests are travelling.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613832048,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-14 16:08:22"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:50:29",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632037136,
                    "naive_sentiment": -5,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 16114228,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:50:29",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is it there an extra bed for the third guest in the superior sea facing room....as we are 3 adults?..secondly, it's my daughter's birthday can I order a cake....can the hotel help me with it..?  Last but not the least, which restaurants are there in the hotel  premises?",
                    "answer": "If the booking is made on triple occupancy an extra bed will be provided for the third guest. Kindly do send us the request directly from your booking.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570629,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-19 07:38:56"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-31 08:33:18",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 35596920,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-31 08:33:18",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1680227607,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -7,
                    "answer": "As per hotel policy, maximum 3 guests in a room (including children).  In event of 4 guests, 2 rooms must be booked.",
                    "question": "My family including my wife, 9 year old baby boy and 5 year old a baby girl. Is it possible that we will stay together in one room.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1680251598,
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-31 01:53:27",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2019-11-20 09:26:49",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1574065119,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -7,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 1662078,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2019-11-20 09:26:49",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "WE need to include lunch & dinner in the package",
                    "answer": "Please be informed that lunch and dinner will be served on Al A Carte.\nRequest you to advise your booking confirmation number in order to advise your further",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-18 08:18:39",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1574242009,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275065,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 15:48:12",
                    "question": "Hi in this three adult and one children of 14 years half bording charges are included?",
                    "answer": "2 separate rooms will need to be booked as we have a maximum of 3 guests in 1 room including children. Over 12 yrs are considered as adults. Rates As per the available package online. Children above 5-12 yrs will be charged additional for the meals.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:51:05",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653925692,
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:51:05",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25307607,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 12:59:54",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 24631972,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 12:59:54",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652692056,
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answer": "We can make arrangements for your special occassion at an additional charge. Kindly contact the hotel directly.",
                    "question": "Hi, purpose of travel is to celebrate my 20th marriage Anniversari, do u have any special offer for such event.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792394,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-16 09:07:36",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830537,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-03 07:40:17",
                    "answer": "Yes charges apply.",
                    "question": "Minibar is chargeable?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:15:37",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 22848124,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1648971617,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:15:37"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Depends on the package booked. Please write directly from the booking made.",
                    "question": "I want to know cancellation policy of Taj hotels",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-06 11:47:07",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712211,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15621729,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:23:31",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630928827,
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:23:31"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Complimentary standard wi-fi for 4 devices is available.",
                    "question": "is wifi available in rooms ? if yes is it free or chargeable",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887583,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-11 04:36:35",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:46:23",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -11,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610339795,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 6398385,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:46:23",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:41:07",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:41:07",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634654436,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -13,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 17239775,
                    "question": "Do you provide an extra bed on request for an extra person",
                    "answer": "If the booking is on double occupancy you can amend the same to triple occupancy and an extra bed will be provided automatically for the third guest.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907267,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-19 14:40:36",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Wish to book 1 night stay on  July 16. We are residing in Mumbai and haven’t travelled abroad in last few years. Is it possible to book now?",
                    "answer": "Yes you may book for 16th July now.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1622563117,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-01 15:52:07",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 10647083,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-01 15:58:37",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1622562727,
                    "naive_sentiment": -13,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-01 15:58:37"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:35:12",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 6900441,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:35:12",
                    "naive_sentiment": -13,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612435753,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question": "Lunch & Dinner included are buffet????",
                    "answer": "Set meal menu ",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539312,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-04 10:49:13",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "As per government advisories, certain services, including but not limited to spa, salon, Swimming Pool, fitness center, may be non-operational. The health and safety of our guests and associates is our utmost priority.",
                    "question": "Is there a swimming pool and is it functional",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1617773339,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-28 17:45:48",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-07 05:28:59",
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "naive_sentiment": -15,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616953548,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8358537,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-07 05:28:59",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "We can offer a confirmed late check-out by 17:00 hrs at an additional quarter days charge plus taxes.",
                    "question": "hi I am traveling with my parents my check-in time ll be 5pm ,can I get 24hrs fr my check out.",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-15 20:16:16",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137510,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:25:10",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1637007376,
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18224318,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:25:10",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:08:53",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:08:53",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628447631,
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 14273459,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question": "Is there a poo",
                    "answer": "Pool services are currently non operational.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040133,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-08 18:33:51",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584424,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 12:50:46",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Please check the wesite for details for the same according to your stay dates.",
                    "question": "How much extra for all meals.",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12268727,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625316646,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:13:44",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:13:44",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:34:45",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6916859,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:34:45",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612495581,
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question": "Hi... is this hotel couple friendly..",
                    "answer": "We do allow couples",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539285,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-05 03:26:21",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:12:15",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:12:15",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642946200,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 20348320,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President - IHCL Seleqtions, is a pet friendly hotel in case you wish to travel with your companion ",
                    "question": "Hi I am traveling with my pet. Will you allow it?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830335,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-23 13:56:40",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "how do u differentiate between Tower & palace rooms? how would I know prior check in where am I going to get placed? is swimming pool operational now?",
                    "answer": "The Taj Mahal Tower is the modern hotel while the Taj Mahal Palace is the Heritage hotel. It would depend on the hotel you choose to book at. The pool service is non-operational.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351221,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-26 20:49:41",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:40:21",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632689381,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 16403045,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:40:21",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-13 11:06:16",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040414,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is this a pet friendly hotel",
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President - IHCL Seleqtions, is a pet friendly hotel in case you wish to travel with your companion",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:13:34",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 14538035,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628852776,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:13:34"
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5954398,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608300286,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-19 14:48:34",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-19 14:48:34",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608389314,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-18 14:04:46",
                    "answer": "There is only a walk in shower in the Superior and Deluxe room category. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and in the rooms and suites at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Kindly place a request for the same.",
                    "question": "Is there is a bath tub in the room?"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-11-22 21:57:23",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 5527871,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-11-22 21:57:23",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1605966736,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President - IHCL Seleqtions, is a pet friendly hotel in case you wish to travel with your companion.",
                    "question": "Hi Team,\n\nThis is Yogesh here. I want planning book a suite with my wife and my pet Solo (a pug). Heard that our property is a pet friendly property.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1606082243,
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-21 13:52:16",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137453,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-12 03:33:42",
                    "answer": "Please do check the same on the taj Hotels web site as we are unable to share contact details on the chat service.",
                    "question": "contact details",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636688022,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -23,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:24:13",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18095848,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:24:13",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Yes its on an A La Carte basis.",
                    "question": "Are there charges levied on products consumed from the minibar?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905937,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-29 12:24:57",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:05:37",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:05:37",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627561497,
                    "naive_sentiment": -23,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13703791
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-08 08:32:41",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 17927084,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-08 08:32:41",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636299734,
                    "naive_sentiment": -25,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question": "Hi, can you bring 2 local resident guest during stay for an hour? Also, is outside customized birthday cake allowed in room ?",
                    "answer": "N2 non resident guests can certainly visit. Kindly contact the duty manager for the same. Outside cake would be allowed in the room only.",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-07 15:42:14",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1636360361,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Do you provide drivers accommodations?",
                    "answer": "A seperate room reservation will need to be processed for the driver.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827063,
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-13 03:21:58",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:24:23",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644722518,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -27,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 21123054,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:24:23",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Are your swimming pools operational?",
                    "answer": "Current guidelines in Maharashtra do not permit the usage of the swimming pool. Keeping this in mind, the hotel is in the process of upgrading our product.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138706,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-10 10:35:20",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:18:26",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:18:26",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639132520,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -27,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18977074
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570643,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-19 16:46:05",
                    "question": "Can we do payment by credit card?",
                    "answer": "Payment can be made by credit card.",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 16132067,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632069965,
                    "naive_sentiment": -27,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:50:43",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:50:43",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830483,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-07 09:38:00",
                    "answer": "Outsice alcohol can be consumed in the room only.",
                    "question": "hi can we carry our own liquor to room , I mean if we can consume in our room ....",
                    "question_id": 23014384,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649324280,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:14:43",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:14:43",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644826978,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-12 14:44:50",
                    "question": "Half board included means",
                    "answer": "Half board includes breakfast and one major set meal at a pre-designated venue.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641998690,
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:22:58",
                    "question_id": 19961864,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:22:58",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:15:07",
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621323300,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 10012086,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:15:07",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hello, does this superior room has bathtub?",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walkin shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354507,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-18 07:35:00"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walkin shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "Hie is there a bath tub in the room?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354461,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-09 06:45:39",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 9653299,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:14:21",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620542739,
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:14:21"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-08 07:16:41",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610199968,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Do you have bath tub ?",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6342418,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610090201,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-09 13:46:08",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-09 13:46:08",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-05 19:26:31",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686040611,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "hi \ndo you have a driver to pick me up from the airport?",
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER CAR PER WAY):  (Rates are subject to change) - SUV: INR 4950/- plus 12% GST\nThe flight details and guest contact number in case the airport transfers needs to be arranged (minimum 24 hours prior intimation is needed). \n",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-06 08:36:51",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1685993191,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-06 08:36:51",
                    "question_id": 37218369,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653843993,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-20 17:36:55",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "Hi are there bath tubs cause I cannot see it in the pictures and also can we get our own alcohol bottles ?",
                    "question_id": 24849072,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653068215,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:06:33",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:06:33",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 19924862,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:10:18",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641911567,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:10:18",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "does every room have bathtub ?",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-11 14:32:47",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830218,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18750432,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:31:58",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638453559,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:31:58",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "hi do we have bath tub in all the rooms",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952318,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-02 13:59:19"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-13 09:49:58",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636659299,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 18085760,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-13 09:49:58",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "is there a bathtub",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1636796998,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-11 19:34:59"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:42:27",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:42:27",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1635042872,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 17408906,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "Which sea facing rooms have bathtub facility?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907347,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-24 02:34:32",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Does this room come with bath tub",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907224,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-17 11:35:39",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 17153271,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:40:24",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634470539,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:40:24"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Does superior room has a bath tub",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570658,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-20 19:49:21",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:50:58",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 16178465,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:50:58",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632167361,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708
                },
                {
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630387837,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-31 13:12:36",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15367515,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-31 13:12:36",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1630415556,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-31 05:30:37",
                    "question": "Is bathtub available in taj mahal tower superior city view room?",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai."
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:09:13",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629218500,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:09:13",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14753793,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629464953,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-17 16:41:40",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "does this room have bath tub ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "Hi. Do you have bathtub?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-15 17:46:00",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629464946,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 14650520,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:09:06",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629049560,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:09:06"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176179,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-02 15:08:09",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "I want a bath tub",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 13926703,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627916889,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:09:39",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:09:39",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hi do you have a bathtub in superior room",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-24 08:22:00",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627231035,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:37:15",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13413722,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:37:15",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627114920,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627230907,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-25 14:10:00",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "is there a bath tub",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627222200,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:35:07",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 13476182,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:35:07",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13176619,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-20 14:01:52",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626725809,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-20 14:01:52",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "does this rooms have bathtub?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-19 20:16:49",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626789712,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-17 14:26:09",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626527698,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-17 14:26:09",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13048479,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626531969,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-17 13:14:58",
                    "question": "Is there a bathtub available",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "question": "Does the room have a bath tub",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626278870,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-07 02:22:21",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-14 16:07:50",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-14 16:07:50",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1623032541,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 10911078
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hi, do you have bathtub in this room ?",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584295,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-04 21:11:17",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12351667,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:11:35",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625433077,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:11:35"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:09:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1622316873,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:09:31",
                    "question_id": 10519913,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584171,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-29 19:34:33",
                    "question": "Do all the rooms have tubs in the bathroom",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:36:39",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624384391,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:36:39",
                    "question_id": 11696137,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624512999,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-22 17:53:11",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. ",
                    "question": "Hey I need a room with bathtub & smoking in room is okay?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "will every room have a bathtub. where can I check if not",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room categories at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walki-n shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619410317,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-25 16:24:24",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 9177537,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-26 04:11:57",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1619367864,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-26 04:11:57"
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 8730665,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618090381,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-11 06:49:04",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-11 06:49:04",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1618123744,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-10 21:33:01",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room categories at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "Hi, do your rooms have a bath tub?"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 6493161,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:45:54",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610721259,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:45:54",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Two seperate rooms will need to be reserved as we have a maximum occupancy of three guest including children. Children twelve years and above are considered as adults. Once the booking has been processed the required information will be shared ",
                    "question": "Me n my husband wish to visit with our 2 daughter, age 14 n 9, so can we accommodate in one single room, what will be the price. And to book a room what documents are needed. As we live in Thane, Maharashtra.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887554,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-15 14:34:19",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-31 07:44:40",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907367,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Please check the web site.",
                    "question": "Hi Sir\n\nwhat is your room rate for double room with twin beds",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -35,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1635666280,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:42:47",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 17670113,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:42:47",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628885004,
                    "naive_sentiment": -37,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 11:51:09",
                    "question_id": 14564082,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 11:51:09",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-13 20:03:24",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629028269,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "do you have bathtub 🛁",
                    "answer": "We do have rooms with bath tub in Taj Mahal Palace . In the Taj Mahal Tower we have only Apollo suites with bath tub ."
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly through your reservation messaging option.",
                    "question": "Hey I wana celebrate my partner's birthday there is any special facilities for the same ???",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-13 21:02:26",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712049,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:20:49",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -39,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631566946,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 15917073,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:20:49",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539342,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-03 15:22:24",
                    "question": "Is gateway of india view can be captured from the room",
                    "answer": "Yes you can click pictures from your mobile phone but you will have a top view.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:35:42",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612365744,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -39,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:35:42",
                    "question_id": 6883061,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2022-11-10 18:58:27",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229402,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Hello we land at 1 am in the morning and we will likely be at the property around 3 am. Is that possible to check in at that time?",
                    "answer": "All arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1668106707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:03:22",
                    "question_id": 32418480,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:03:22",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is breakfast included and is the pool functional",
                    "answer": "Kindly refer to your package inclusions for the breakfast. The pool is non operations as per Government directives.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899709,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-22 12:34:35",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:55:09",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14981432,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:55:09",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629635675,
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629828124,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:54:26",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15093618,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:54:26",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899666,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-24 18:02:04",
                    "question": "Can I carry a bottle of wine from outside shop into my room?",
                    "answer": "You can certainly get a wine bottle from outside to consume in your room only."
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly. We have day use rooms for upto 5 hours only.",
                    "question": "Can we checkinn at 11 am \nStay till 9 pm",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088114,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-12 10:52:12",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:08:34",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12761187,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:08:34",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626087132,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-27 11:35:44",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1611748881,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is the pool operational,??",
                    "answer": "Due to the pandemic the swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. ",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-27 12:01:21",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611747344,
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-27 12:01:21",
                    "question_id": 6735269,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-20 05:49:33",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 37518881,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-20 05:49:33",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1687060327,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "answer": "You may make the payment in advance towards room charges and taxes and an advance towards extras spend during the stay too ",
                    "question": "Can I make a reservation for my parents where I make the entire payment upfront so that my parents are not bothered during their stay?",
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-18 03:52:07",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1687240173,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138724,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-09 07:05:33",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "do you have / provide bed for  drivers night stay arrangement ?",
                    "answer": "A seperate room reservation will need to be made.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:18:44",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639033533,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:18:44",
                    "question_id": 18943851,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631018334,
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:23:08",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 15666503,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:23:08",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-07 12:38:54",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712188,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "The pool services are non operational due to government policy.",
                    "question": "If staying at the the tower is it possible to use the Taj Mahal pool?\nOr can you use the Taj Mahal hotel pool if you have lunch or a spa treatment?"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kindly contact our Catering Sales team directly by calling the hotel boardline.",
                    "question": "want to arrange a marriage involving 50 persons on 2nd May. Need a banquet hall. please quote with vegetarian lunch for 50 pax & other detail",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912919,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-19 15:46:10",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:28:39",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:28:39",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616168770,
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8096354
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-08-28 04:33:43",
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1692588985,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 39142102,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-08-28 04:33:43",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Visitor are allowed from morning 0900 hrs. To 2000 hrs",
                    "question": "What are visitors timing",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1693197223,
                    "asked_at": "2023-08-21 03:36:25",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:57:47",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 19152526,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639638227,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:57:47",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599067,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-16 07:03:47",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Certain rooms have smart TV's.",
                    "question": "Does this room have a smart TV ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 18637155,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-02 05:21:53",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638128067,
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-02 05:21:53",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hi,\nis there any complimentary on birthday",
                    "answer": "We can make arrangements at cost as per the Celebration menu. Please do write to us directly from your booking to share the same.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638422513,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-28 19:34:27"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:10:43",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12631842,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:10:43",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625855052,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question": "Does the Superior Room have Bath tub??",
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Please request the same when bookin",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088243,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-09 18:24:12",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951973,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-04 06:11:54",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "The Superior & Deluxe room categories only have walk in showers while the Apollo Suite and rooms at the Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai have bathtubs.",
                    "question": "Do you have bathubs in each and every bathroom?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:46:13",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614838314,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:46:13",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7636136,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951967,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-04 06:00:00",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is there is bath tub is available  in superiors city view rooms",
                    "answer": "The Superior & Deluxe room categories only have walk in showers while the Apollo Suite and rooms at the Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai have bathtubs.",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7635988,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614837600,
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:46:07",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:46:07",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4948003,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601839803,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:14:09",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:14:09",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422449,
                    "asked_at": "2020-10-04 19:30:03",
                    "answer": "Non residential guests are not allowed on guest floors. You can meet them at the restaurant. A prior table reservation will be required for them to enter the hotel.",
                    "question": "I am booking a room for meeting.. My other 2 clients are allowed to visit me in my room?"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653844063,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-27 09:56:17",
                    "question": "Hello,\nWe booked the non-board package.\nHow much will it cost to add only breakfast for one day per person ? \nThank you.",
                    "answer": "Breakfast will be chargeable at INR. 1200+18% taxes per person per day for our inhouse guests.",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25157991,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653645377,
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:43",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:43",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626028869,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:09:32",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12731636,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:09:32",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088172,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-11 18:41:09",
                    "answer": "We can assit with birthday celebrations at charge. Please do request the same from your booking. We can share the menu for your perusal.",
                    "question": "Hi, can we celebrate a birthday among two people only?"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Please message directly from your booking.",
                    "question": "I have booked in 2 adults but booking is confirmed sand to my mail.1 parson please confirm tome",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-03 10:20:03",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831779,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:36:19",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:36:19",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612347603,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 6877495,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899596,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-22 07:59:13",
                    "answer": "You can certianly get outside liquor and pre-manufactured food (like chips, etc) into the room only. However outside food from other restaurants, etc. is not allowed. Kindly contact the Duty Mnager/ Front Office team for further clarification.",
                    "question": "Is outside liquor/food allowed to be taken into the room?",
                    "question_id": 14971114,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629619153,
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:53:16",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:53:16",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618248114,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-13 04:00:42",
                    "question_id": 8782863,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-13 04:00:42",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1618286442,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-12 17:21:54",
                    "question": "Do you have proper pure vegetarian food ?",
                    "answer": "Dear guest, we do have vegetarina food at the hotel. Once the booking has been processed do mention your preference for vegetarian food to note the same."
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 5541831,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-11-22 22:00:27",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1606059683,
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-11-22 22:00:27",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hi my check in time is 2pm so will you be able to serve us breakfast in room ?",
                    "answer": "Breakfast can be ordered in the room on an A La Carte basis. In-room dining service will be available from 07:00 hrs. to 23:30 hrs.",
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-22 15:41:23",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1606082427,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-20 14:53:08",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-20 14:53:08",
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1603142989,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 5160587,
                    "question": "Can I get a smoking room?",
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, Kindly do request for the same once the booking has been made through the contact the hotel option.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1603205588,
                    "asked_at": "2020-10-19 21:29:49",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-17 10:31:13",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792240,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "We can make arrangements for a special occassion at an additional charge. Please contact the hotel directly for the details of the same.",
                    "question": "I am planning to book a room for a day in June. Would the hotel Be charging extra amount if we need the room decorated a little for Birthday purpose?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 12:57:20",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 24686511,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652783473,
                    "naive_sentiment": -51,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 12:57:20"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644826932,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-05 19:33:00",
                    "answer": "The parking is around the hotel vicinity. For further queries kindly contact the Duty Manageer at the hotel directly.",
                    "question": "Can you please clarify what do you mean when you say free public parking at location nearby? Is it a safe and secured parking?",
                    "question_id": 19731643,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641411180,
                    "naive_sentiment": -51,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:22:12",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:22:12",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 18151367,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:24:44",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636832881,
                    "naive_sentiment": -53,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:24:44",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "wats they square foot of room",
                    "answer": "The Superior Room City View King Bed is 26 m² or 279 sq ft.",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137484,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-13 19:48:01"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:11:59",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 20218909,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642613117,
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:11:59",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830319,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-19 17:25:17",
                    "answer": "Post booking, you can get in touch us and we can share the payment link.",
                    "question": "Hi there. I want to book a room for a couple as treat from me. I want to make full payment when I book it - prepayment, is that possible? Thanks",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-25 09:32:54",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912878,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite or in the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question": "Is there a bath tub in the room?",
                    "question_id": 8265811,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616664774,
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:27:58",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:27:58",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "It will be on an A La Carte basis at additional charge.",
                    "question": "can I get my breakfast in bed?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614952014,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-27 10:08:04",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 7498115,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:46:54",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614420484,
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:46:54"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 6652846,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-01 13:51:13",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611379719,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-01 13:51:13",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Appolo suit is in taj tower or taj palace",
                    "answer": "Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612187473,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-23 05:28:39"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai",
                    "question": "Is this room the tower or mahal side ?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610622591,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-11 14:15:35",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-14 11:09:51",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610374535,
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6405815,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-14 11:09:51",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 11:51:55",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628899892,
                    "naive_sentiment": -59,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14572834,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 11:51:55",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "No Deluxe rooms do not have bath tub , only Apoll suites in the Tower have bath tub.",
                    "question": "There is a bath tub in deluxe room?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629028315,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-14 00:11:32",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:10:24",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628023712,
                    "naive_sentiment": -59,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14007859,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:10:24",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior & Deluxe rooms, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Kindly contact the hotel directly for the 2nd query.\n",
                    "question": "Is there bath tub in superior room? Which amenities are currently available?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176224,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-03 20:48:32"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:24:44",
                    "naive_sentiment": -61,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644661305,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 21097162,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:24:44",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hello team,\nhow can I arrange a candle light dinner?",
                    "answer": "Please contact the Food 7 beverages team at the hotel boardline directly",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827084,
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-12 10:21:45",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-17 05:53:56",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-17 05:53:56",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1678967426,
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 35257743,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answer": "Extra bed can be provided at an additional charge.\nDinner will be a set meal in a pre-designated venue",
                    "question": "For 3 adults in one room is there an extra bed for the 3rd person\nAlso if we have breakfast and dinner included where is the dinner ? In any restaurant of our choosing ?\n",
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-16 11:50:26",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1679032436,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hi\nAre the swimming pool and fitness centre open?  I am hoping to come in January or February 2022",
                    "answer": "Current guidelines in Maharashtra do not permit the usage of the swimming pool. The Gymnasium (lockers and changing facility) is operational from 07:00 to 22:00 hrs daily. The steam and shower facilities are currently not available as per guidelines.",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-26 17:54:01",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599231,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 10:00:31",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1640541241,
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 19404584,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 10:00:31",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Please book it via the site",
                    "question": "I want a room for 4 adults or 2 rooms for 2 guests each.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465103,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-19 05:50:09",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:11:43",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:11:43",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629352209,
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14833500
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-16 07:57:31",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626531951,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "car parking facility is available ? need to book for a day as my son is bored sitting in the house for more than a year now. please reply.",
                    "answer": "Parking is around the hotel vicinity or the lane behind the hotel B K Boman Mehram Marg and is at the owner’s risk or alternately there is a BMC pay & park is available opposite Regal Cinema that you can opt for.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626422251,
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-17 14:25:51",
                    "question_id": 12985598,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-17 14:25:51",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 7556435,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:44:41",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614606911,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:44:41",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "We can confirm an early check-in at 08:00 hrs at an addiitonal half day's charge. For Arrivals prior to 08:00 hrs you will have to pre-book your room from the previous night.",
                    "question": "We will be arriving at about 0300, is it possible to check in at 0600.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951881,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-01 13:55:11",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1677827576,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-03 08:28:06",
                    "question_id": 34954152,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-03 08:28:06",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677832086,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-03 07:12:56",
                    "answer": "The Deluxe room sea view category does not have twin bedded room. ",
                    "question": "Hi, do your deluxe room sea view come in twin beds?"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:12:19",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 9645974,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:12:19",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620509293,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "answer": "Non resident guests are currently not allowed as per government policy.",
                    "question": "Guest would be allowed during stay ?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354339,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-08 21:28:13",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 5796560,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-11 13:47:15",
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607534259,
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-11 13:47:15",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "The Superior and Deluxe categories have only a walk in shower and does not have a bathtub. The Apollo Suite has a bathtub and a walk in shower.",
                    "question": "Bath tab is available in all the rooms or in deluxe and above??",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607694435,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-09 17:17:39"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is there a bathtub ? and is it a sea view ?",
                    "answer": " Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower & the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Its is a City view room as per description.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040187,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-11 15:04:19",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:09:47",
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628694259,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14438433,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:09:47",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14270881,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:08:36",
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628444902,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:08:36",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "Celebrations can be arranged at an additional charge.",
                    "question": "Will you provide a small complimentary birthday cake? for one of the guest's birthday?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040116,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-08 17:48:22",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608881241,
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:30:51",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6061173,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:30:51",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831451,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-25 07:27:21",
                    "question": "Is there a bath tub?",
                    "answer": "Only walk-in shower."
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-25 15:19:47",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831446,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Does this room have a bath tub?",
                    "answer": "Only walk-in shower.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608909587,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:30:46",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 6065939,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:30:46",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:27:06",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616751029,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -69,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:27:06",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8294874,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912826,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-26 09:30:29",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is the swimming pool operational and also do you have interconnecting rooms",
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. At the Taj Mahal Tower we have limited interconnecting room sets in the Superior and Deluxe room categories with one room being a sea view and the other a city view.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1679032471,
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-16 20:32:35",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Arrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate",
                    "question": "Since we are arriving early morning in Bombay, would it be possible to check in at about 9:30- 10 am?",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1678998755,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-17 05:54:31",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 35268001,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-17 05:54:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952382,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-06 08:16:04",
                    "question": "Hello,\n\nDo you have quarantine rooms? If yes how can we book it",
                    "answer": "Please contact the hotel directly",
                    "question_id": 18852140,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638778564,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:33:02",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:33:02",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905826,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-01 12:53:35",
                    "answer": "Please do note the Disinfection services for the vehicle with valet parking is available at a charge of INR 300 per visit. Parking is around the hotel vicinity or the lane behind the hotel B K Boman Mehram Marg and is at the owner’s risk. ",
                    "question": "Free Parking within the hotel is available for guests?",
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627822415,
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:03:46",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 13859921,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:03:46",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8203913,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616491867,
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:28:07",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:28:07",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912887,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-23 09:31:07",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Hello is your swimming pool operational due to COVID ?",
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. "
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:13:25",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 23221156,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:13:25",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649772331,
                    "naive_sentiment": -73,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answer": "Please get in touch directly",
                    "question": "How about honeymoon suit? \nWhat are check-in and check-out charges? \nWhat are inclusions and exclusions after paying booking amount? \nWhat are the facilities with additional charges?",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830405,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-12 14:05:31",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Please contact the Food & Beverages team by directly calling the hotel.",
                    "question": "rate for buffet dinner",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137389,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-12 03:31:16",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:23:09",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:23:09",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636687876,
                    "naive_sentiment": -75,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18095810
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do u have parking facilities? Is valet parking chargeable ?",
                    "answer": "Valet parking facility is available. Overnight parking is available at a charge",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234384,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-22 04:23:54",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:26:24",
                    "language": "en",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:26:24",
                    "naive_sentiment": -77,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1655871834,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 26426182
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:16:02",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question_id": 28270463,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1658819006,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:16:02",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233762,
                    "asked_at": "2022-07-26 07:03:26",
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "question": "What are early checkin charges?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660576965,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:13:01",
                    "question_id": 29338209,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:13:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233581,
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-15 15:22:45",
                    "question": "If i arrived early around 10 am is it possible to check in?",
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "question": "Hello, I’ll land at 4am is it possible to check in early morning?",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233566,
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-12 17:56:41",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:12:46",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 29207553,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:12:46",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660327001,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79
                },
                {
                    "question": "can I check in at 10am in morning",
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate",
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-12 06:02:30",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233558,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:12:38",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 29177621,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:12:38",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660284150,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 33522377,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:48:55",
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1672700031,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:48:55",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "We need 1 room for 3 days - but we will be arriving 5 am in morning. Can we get room at that time . After paying  some nominal charges",
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228535,
                    "asked_at": "2023-01-02 22:53:51"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 20178462,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:11:06",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642524074,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:11:06",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hello,\n\nDo you offer airport transfers?\n\nThanks.",
                    "answer": "At charge. Please revert from your booking directly.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830266,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-18 16:41:14",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610622462,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-29 18:27:43",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Does the bathroom have a bathtub",
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available onli in the Apollo Suite at Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1609266463,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -81,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-14 11:07:42",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 6151955,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-14 11:07:42",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-14 11:08:07",
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610544621,
                    "naive_sentiment": -83,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 6449006,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-14 11:08:07",
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "do u have bathtub",
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available only in the Apollo Suite at Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610622487,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-13 13:30:21"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-05-20 11:32:40",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 36822492,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-05-20 11:32:40",
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1684561278,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question": "Person paying for one adult for a deluxe room, can be/she can invite guests?",
                    "answer": "No visitors are allowed beyond 21:00hrs ",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1684582360,
                    "asked_at": "2023-05-20 05:41:18",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 30944842,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:28:33",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1663941357,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:28:33",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "No visitors are allowed beyond 21:00hrs ",
                    "question": "Hi can my family visit me in my room when i am staying here?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234513,
                    "asked_at": "2022-09-23 13:55:57",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "answer": "The rooms are air conditioned",
                    "question": "Is there fen along with ac in room??",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227629,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-07 03:59:18",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:33:49",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25675751,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:33:49",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654574358,
                    "naive_sentiment": -85
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-10 19:12:14",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827174,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is swimming pool usage available again?",
                    "answer": "The hotel is in the process of upgrading our product; swimming pool is under renovation till further notice.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:26:14",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644520334,
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:26:14",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 21043932,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827167,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-11 08:43:07",
                    "answer": "The hotel is in the process of upgrading our product; swimming pool is under renovation till further notice.",
                    "question": "Is pool open ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:26:07",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644568987,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:26:07",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 21060495,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088276,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-09 17:40:48",
                    "answer": "Non resident guests are not allowed in the guest rooms due to the current scenario as per hotel policy.",
                    "question": "guest are allow in room ???",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625852448,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:11:16",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12629838,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:11:16",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-23 07:02:46",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 10171541,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621627162,
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-23 07:02:46",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621753366,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-21 19:59:22",
                    "question": "I am not able to find any room which has bathtub and also shower area",
                    "answer": "Apollo Suite has a bath tub, walk-in shower and sea view. ",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:47:37",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 34642877,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:47:37",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1676658391,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "answer": "The rooms can accommodate maximum 3 guests(including children). We can provide extra roll away bed at an additional charge.",
                    "question": "hi. can you set up an extra bed for the 3rd adult ? or do you have rooms with 2 doubles ?",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228457,
                    "asked_at": "2023-02-17 18:26:31",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1630774878,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-04 16:56:40",
                    "question": "Do you have the facility for driver accommodation and whether driver can stay in car. Is the parking inside the premises",
                    "answer": "We do not have a facility for driver accomodation. An additional room will need to be booked.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630774600,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-04 17:01:18",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 15556535,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-04 17:01:18",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hello. I would like to book a room for my friend who is visiting from the USA. What are the guidelines? Can he check in directly after arrival?",
                    "answer": "Please do contact the hotel directly.",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831687,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-20 16:08:40",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:34:47",
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611158920,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6604304,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:34:47",
                    "language": "en"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831680,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-24 14:17:19",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question": "Is there any discount for Indian Army soldiers ?",
                    "answer": "Please do contact the hotel directly.",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:34:40",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 6677144,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611497839,
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:34:40"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 35116170,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-11 06:06:37",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1678446578,
                    "naive_sentiment": -89,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-11 06:06:37",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Does the room have a bathtub ?",
                    "answer": "The Deluxe Room Sea view has a shower cubicle. It does not have bathtub",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1678514797,
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-10 11:09:38",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1676547961,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2023-02-08 05:23:45",
                    "answer": "•\tCheck-outs between 14:00-16:00hrs will be charged at 25% of the room rate, and those between 16:00-18:00hrs will be charged at 50% of the room rate.\n•\tAny departures post 18:00hrs will be charged for the full night.",
                    "question": "Hi. Is there an option of late check out? At what time would that be and what is the extra cost for it?",
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 34415779,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1675833825,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -89,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-16 11:46:01",
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-16 11:46:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1689417870,
                    "asked_at": "2023-07-12 18:55:45",
                    "question": "Can 3 adults and 1 child (5years old) stay in one Deluxe room? What are the charges for extra bed? Thanks",
                    "answer": "Maximum 3 guest (including children) can be accommodated. For 3 adults and a child, 2 rooms need to be booked. ",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2023-07-15 10:44:30",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 38155996,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1689188145,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -91,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-07-15 10:44:30"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599179,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-25 05:14:50",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer": "Our rooms can accomodate 3 adults as long as the booking is processed on triple occupancy except the Taj Club rooms.",
                    "question": "We are a family of 3. Do you have any rooms that can accommodate 3 adults?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:59:39",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1640409290,
                    "naive_sentiment": -91,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:59:39",
                    "question_id": 19366730,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 20053163,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:10:42",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -93,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642232514,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:10:42",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is operational from 0600 hours to 0900 hours, 12 noon to 1500 hours and 1800 hours to 2100 hours daily.",
                    "question": "swimming pool is accessible",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830242,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-15 07:41:54",
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:15:11",
                    "naive_sentiment": -95,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1604250616,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 5295525,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:15:11",
                    "language": "en",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hii i am coming from goa and my flight will arrive at 7 am. I need early checkin at 8 am.",
                    "answer": "The same can be confirmed at an additional half days charge. Kindly do request the same on your booking request. ",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422511,
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-01 17:10:16"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:48:25",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "en",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1674473752,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -97,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:48:25",
                    "question_id": 34028298,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228505,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "asked_at": "2023-01-23 11:35:52",
                    "answer": "Extra roll away bed can be provide maximum one, at an additional charge",
                    "question": "is there extra beds?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831802,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-14 14:18:18",
                    "question": "Do you have sea view room spa packages for 1 night ?",
                    "answer": "Regret that Spa is not a part of the package.",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "question_id": 7153398,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613312298,
                    "naive_sentiment": -97,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:36:42",
                    "language": "en",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:36:42",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                }
            ],
            "opted_out_of_q_and_a": 0,
            "hotel_id": "74717",
            "collect_q_and_a_questions": 1
        },
        "optional": {
            "hotel_id": "74717",
            "success": 1,
            "average_response_time_in_seconds": 2414041,
            "average_response_time": "This property usually replies within a few days",
            "collect_q_and_a_questions": 1,
            "q_and_a_pairs": [
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there a hand shower",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2019-10-23 13:04:42",
                    "answered_at": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1571923294,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1571835882,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question_id": 1489869,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2019-10-24 13:21:34",
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "answer": "Yes",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 29
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hi i have elderly parents and they would arrive in domestic flight and would be travelling on international flight . do you offer early check in around 11am?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-08-24 00:35:18",
                    "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1598246897,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1598229318,
                    "question_id": 4386257,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:28:17",
                    "votes": 27,
                    "answer": "Yes sir, we can provide the same subject to availability at the time of arrival.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello. Do you have swimming pool and is it available to use now? Best regards, Tatiana",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-26 06:41:21",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653844021,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653547281,
                    "question_id": 25104804,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:01",
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is operational from 06:00 to 22:00 hours daily.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 25
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question_id": 1400862,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The same can be arranged at an additional cost.",
                    "votes": 24,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:11:39",
                    "naive_sentiment": -77,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2019-09-30 18:16:38",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:11:39",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "How do I organise a pick up from the airport when I arrive",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1569867398,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422299,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1598246788,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1555235763,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "With out married couples are allowed or no",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2019-04-14 09:56:03",
                    "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:26:28",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:26:28",
                    "naive_sentiment": -5,
                    "answer": "Yes. the guests are allowed.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 23,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 35017,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-13 21:08:18",
                    "answered_at": "2019-11-18 14:16:58",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi \nPete here. I'm traveling with my teenage daughter. I'm interested in a room with 2 beds. from 12/27-12/31. \ndo you have a room like that? \nthank you",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1573679298,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1574086618,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 1629646,
                    "answer": "We have limited twin beds in the Superior / Deluxe city view category in the Taj Mahal Tower and Luxury Grand City view room in the Taj Mahal Palace. In case, it’s not available, we can arrange for a Hollywood twin set up, where there are 02 separate duvets placed on one king bed. Request you to kindly place a request for the same once your reservation has been processed.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 20,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2019-11-18 14:16:58",
                    "naive_sentiment": -23
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-11 15:40:40",
                    "naive_sentiment": -11,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, An additional room will need to be booked.",
                    "votes": 17,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 15642,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1602430840,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1554017040,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Can driver have room to stay",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-11 15:40:40",
                    "asked_at": "2019-03-31 07:24:00"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2019-04-04 17:42:52",
                    "answered_at": "2020-08-24 05:26:11",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Prepayment is possible?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1554399772,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1598246771,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 22290,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes, prepayment via a secure payment link is possible.",
                    "votes": 14,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-08-24 05:26:11",
                    "naive_sentiment": 87
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 4887537,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answer": "Yes sir, we can provide pure vegetarian food.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 13,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-09-30 07:11:37",
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-30 07:03:06",
                    "answered_at": "2020-09-30 07:11:37",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Pure vegetarian food available?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601449386,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1601449897,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-17 11:34:07",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:43:30",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Breakfast complementary....?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610883247,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887410,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 6529143,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear guest, This depends on the package booked at.",
                    "votes": 9,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:43:30",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Includes a pre-set meal for dinner, breakfast and pre-set meal for lunch at a pre-designated venue. The set meal will be available at the All day dining Shamiana will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 8,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-07 04:29:18",
                    "naive_sentiment": 59,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 9578648,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620336891,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1620361758,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-06 21:34:51",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-07 04:29:18",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Full board meal means"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584281,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625498174,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does the Superior Room Sea View King Bed option come with a stand in balcony?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:11:21",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-05 15:16:14",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:11:21",
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in which a guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "votes": 8,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 12389604,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:11:13",
                    "asked_at": "2019-09-13 06:39:25",
                    "question": "Is there bath tub available in every room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1568356765,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422273,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 1282947,
                    "votes": 7,
                    "answer": "We have walk-in showers only in the Superior and Deluxe room categories.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:11:13"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "if we are booking for full board menu, how it will be served? In room or buffet menu?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-08 06:46:09",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-12 13:38:47",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613137127,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612766769,
                    "question_id": 6984568,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-12 13:38:47",
                    "naive_sentiment": -17,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The set meal is available at the All day dining restaurant Shamiana and will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked. ",
                    "votes": 7
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-19 14:49:28",
                    "votes": 6,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. Due to the current pandemic situation it takes longer to have the room ready (cleaned and sanitised) after a guest checks out and hence appreciate your understanding and co-operation.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 5951101,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608389368,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608285709,
                    "question": "Can you allow late checkout",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-18 10:01:49",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-19 14:49:28",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 7219783,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471721,
                    "answer": "The meals are included in the Suite Surprises package.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 6,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:38:25",
                    "naive_sentiment": 33,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-16 21:25:37",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:38:25",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Lunch inculcated",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613510737,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831905,
                    "room_name": "Apollo Suite Sea View with complimentary one way Airport Transfer and daily evening cocktails at Taj Club Lounge"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-06 17:00:43",
                    "asked_at": "2020-10-06 14:30:12",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is this room Gateway of India facing?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601994612,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1602003643,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 4973338,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 5,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, The room is a city facing room. We would suggest to book the Deluxe Sea view room or the Apollo Suite for panaromic views of the Gateway of India and the harbour. The Supeior Sea view rooms located on the lower floors also has a sea view.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 51,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-06 17:00:43"
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:28:31",
                    "votes": 4,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 25637337,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227311,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654517664,
                    "question": "How much it cost for airport shuttle?Thanks",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-06 12:14:24",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:28:31",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-26 08:44:43",
                    "answered_at": "2020-09-30 07:12:08",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "People coming from kamothe navi mumbai are allowed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601109883,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1601449928,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 4834302,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes, we request you to pre-book and arrive.",
                    "votes": 4,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-09-30 07:12:08",
                    "naive_sentiment": 71
                },
                {
                    "votes": 4,
                    "answer": "The full board package begins with dinner on day of arrival.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 53,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-01 16:00:31",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 10319293,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621935399,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1622563231,
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-01 16:00:31",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-25 09:36:39",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "What is the first meal on the check-in day on full board",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-04 13:46:58",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:19:20",
                    "question": "Bathtub is there?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607089618,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422760,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 5705684,
                    "votes": 4,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Bathtub is available only in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and the rooms in the Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Please do ensure the preference is requested for at the time of booking.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:19:20"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-13 07:46:57",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 17:00:34",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I have a puppy.. allowed?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607845617,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051634,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question_id": 5856380,
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President -IHCL Seleqtions is a pet freindly hotel, in case you wish to travel with your companion.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 4,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 17:00:34",
                    "naive_sentiment": -43
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624225008,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624513163,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:39:23",
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-20 21:36:48",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "After check in at 3:00 pm in to the hotel at what time will be full board meals for existing and other day till 11 pm check out will be served?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out. •\tMeal service timings are as follows : Lunch: 12:30hrs to 15:00hrs & Dinner: 19:00hrs to 23:00hrs.",
                    "votes": 2,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:39:23",
                    "naive_sentiment": 97,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 11600510,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 16215413,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 2,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Smoking rooms are available subject to availability.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:51:19",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:51:19",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-21 18:20:44",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hii is smoking room available",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632248444,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570679
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:09:07",
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Unmarried couple are allowed. Valid photo id proofs will be required at check-in.",
                    "votes": 2,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 10365533,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584147,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1622017996,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Unmarried couples are allowed or not..??",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:09:07",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-26 08:33:16"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234556,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1666467379,
                    "question": "Hi, do you have airport pickup service available? And the cost please?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-10-22 19:36:19",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:29:16",
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:29:16",
                    "votes": 2,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 31862932,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "votes": 2,
                    "answer": "Maximum 3 guests including children can be accommodated in one room, with one extra bed. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-07-12 11:06:06",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 38128479,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1689102098,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1689159966,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2023-07-11 19:01:38",
                    "answered_at": "2023-07-12 11:06:06",
                    "question": "We stayed a few times at your wonderful hotel some years ago. We have 3 teenages now. Is it possible to put an extra bed in the room? Two double+1 bed",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I am asking if the Breakfast is ABF OR CONTINENTAL? n no one is replying.",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:16:03",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-02 12:48:04",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584563,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625230084,
                    "question_id": 12219202,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:16:03",
                    "naive_sentiment": -75,
                    "answer": "Breakfast is on a buffet basis at the All Day Dining Shamiana.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 2
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently non-operational as per government policy. If booked for the Tower you have access to the general public areas like the shopping arcade, the restaurants, etc. However the residential floors are exclusively for the guest",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:48:54",
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 16583477,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1633106218,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351734,
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:48:54",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-01 16:36:58",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi we are looking to book if staying in the tower can we use switch pool and facilities at the palace\nRegards jon"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear guest, the photo id proofs will be required. Individuals with a cough, cold, or a temperature of more than 98.6F or 37.3C will regrettably not be permitted entry into the hotel premises for the safety and security of all concerned. ",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-22 09:22:41",
                    "naive_sentiment": 77,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "question_id": 8833178,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618395897,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619083361,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-22 09:22:41",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-14 10:24:57",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I am a local can I come to stay if yes what all documents are required ?"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 10019315,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.\nWe recommend to arrive by the standard timings to ensure a ready room on arrival.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:14:58",
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:14:58",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-18 11:08:18",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "What is the check in and check out time",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621336098,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354498,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831865,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613493439,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi!\nIs there any option for early check in? Like 11 am in the morning?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-16 16:37:19",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:37:45",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:37:45",
                    "naive_sentiment": 73,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. We recommend to arrive by the standard timings to ensure a ready room on arrival. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 7211237,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612530220,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539101,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:31:41",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-05 13:03:40",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hie do u allow unmarried couples ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes we can accomodate unmarried couples",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:31:41",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 6924533
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887609,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1609669470,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is it facilited with bathroom",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-03 10:24:30",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:46:49",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:46:49",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear guest, the room has a walk in shower and toilet.",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "question_id": 6236868,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613832012,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613479192,
                    "question": "Do you have sea view rooms with one double bed & 1 single bed to accommodate 3 people in one room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:40:12",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-16 12:39:52",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": 51,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:40:12",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answer": "Yes, if the booking is confirmed on triple occupancy an extra bed will be arranged for the third guest.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 7205334,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830464,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649509688,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi.. I need to know about the price of sea view rooms",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:14:24",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-09 13:08:08",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:14:24",
                    "naive_sentiment": 39,
                    "answer": "Please check the site",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 23096482,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you have smoking room and do you have balcony or room with windows that open please let me no thank you",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-22 17:44:12",
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:37:36",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624513056,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624383852,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 11695648,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 39,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:37:36",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We do have smoking rooms. Kindly place a request when processing the booking. We have french windows that open into a balcony that you can comfortably stand in."
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 15971845,
                    "answer": "Depending on the package booked.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:21:01",
                    "naive_sentiment": 33,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-15 09:05:59",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:21:01",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "is breakfast complimentary",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631696759,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712061,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612187535,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612034896,
                    "question": "In this package of 5738/- does it include breakfast ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-01 13:52:15",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-30 19:28:16",
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-01 13:52:15",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answer": "Kindly check the inclusion details of the package selected.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6801321,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes we do have limited twin rooms available in this category.",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:34:10",
                    "naive_sentiment": 19,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 6551644,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610968005,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831650,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-18 11:06:45",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:34:10",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Can i get in this room twine bed"
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 09:59:54",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Half board is breakfast and one major set meal (dinner or lunch) while full board is set meal dinner on the arrival date, buffet breakfast and set lunch on the next day.",
                    "question_id": 11599584,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624528794,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624223907,
                    "question": "What is meant by half board and full board meal?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-20 21:18:27",
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 09:59:54",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1572819117,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422358,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:12:38",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-03 22:11:57",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there a spa in the room?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Spa services are currently non-operational.",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:12:38",
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 1553282,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 23231579,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answer": "You can book the Superior Sea view (closer view of the Gateway of India, the Dleuxe Sea view or the Apollo Suite.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:12:55",
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:12:55",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-12 18:32:26",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, I plan to stay on 7/5/22 for a night. Which room do I book to get a clear view of the Arabian Sea and India Gate",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649788346,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830375
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 22815151,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room.  Two rooms will need to be booked. Please check the charges online.",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:16:04",
                    "naive_sentiment": -7,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-02 08:07:18",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:16:04",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "We are family with 5 adults and 1 kid (7years). 17-22 April / Provide price for ocean facing room with breakfast.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1648886838,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830564
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 7173544,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:37:01",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answer": "Please do check for the all meal inclusive package.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Can breakfast & dinner be provided in package.?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-15 10:11:03",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:37:01",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831821,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613383863
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613762703,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831948,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:39:08",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-19 19:25:03",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, which floors will be the superior room sea view located.?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "3rd-10th floor of the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai.",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:39:08",
                    "naive_sentiment": -25,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 7297748
                },
                {
                    "question": "hi do you tub bath or bath tub in all the rooms ??",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:18:08",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-09 12:49:27",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138688,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639054167,
                    "question_id": 18951407,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:18:08",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai."
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 11636061,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:37:43",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:37:43",
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-21 16:27:36",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "bath tub available and smoking room in this category",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624292856,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624513063,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-16 13:08:16",
                    "naive_sentiment": -39,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 17105953,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634328873,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1634389696,
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-16 13:08:16",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-15 20:14:33",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "how can we book room for day use"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "If the booking has been processed on triple occupancy an extra bed will be provided for the third guest.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 13:00:22",
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 24583876,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652604988,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792422,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 13:00:22",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-15 08:56:28",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "For a triple do you provide a bed for the third person? I see only 1 King size bed. Is there a sofa cum bed or any other arrangement for third person?"
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614603396,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614580902,
                    "question": "is this room  Sea facing?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-01 12:56:36",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-01 06:41:42",
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-01 12:56:36",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please select the Superior Sea view , Deluxe Sea view room or Apollo Suite for a  Sea view room.",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 7547916,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "votes": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite or in the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:23:21",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 8318597,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616827493,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912601,
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-27 06:44:53",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:23:21",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Bath tub is there",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -59,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-01 13:51:43",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answer": "The Superior City view room only has a walk in shower.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 6737462,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612187503,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611755274,
                    "question": "Is there a bath tub in the bathroom?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-27 13:47:54",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-01 13:51:43",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 7502812,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can confirm an early check-in at 08:00 hrs at an addiitonal half day's charge. Arrival prior to 08:00 hrs you will have to pre-book your room from the previous night.",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:44:20",
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:44:20",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-27 14:13:35",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "my flight will arrive early morning, can i check in early or do I need to book for the previous day?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614435215,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951860,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:28:12",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-23 09:20:56",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "is the pool functional",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616491256,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912892,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 8203661,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:28:12",
                    "naive_sentiment": -71
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 6355339,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice as per government guidelines.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -73,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-09 13:45:27",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-08 20:40:32",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-09 13:45:27",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is the swimming pool working?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610138432,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610199927
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471721,
                    "question_id": 12258019,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Apollo Suite is a One bedroom Sea view Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai.",
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:14:22",
                    "naive_sentiment": -75,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 08:30:43",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:14:22",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Apollo suits sea view is in taj mahal palace..!???",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625301043,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584462,
                    "room_name": "Apollo Suite Sea View with complimentary one way Airport Transfer and daily evening cocktails at Taj Club Lounge",
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-04 07:28:43",
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-06 08:34:40",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hi,\nI’m looking to book for 4 nights during Easter. My flight arrives in Mumbai at 8am. Is there a possibility of getting an early check in please?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1685863723,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686040480,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 37178258,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 1,
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-06 08:34:40"
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "price kam karo not affordable please",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-27 19:12:45",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:20:33",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912433,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616872365,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 8334683,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:20:33",
                    "naive_sentiment": 99,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, the rates offered are the best applicable rates.",
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 38933227,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-08-17 05:56:45",
                    "naive_sentiment": 97,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can offer interconnecting rooms, subject to availability on arrival",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do u provide connected rooms",
                    "asked_at": "2023-08-12 08:35:13",
                    "answered_at": "2023-08-17 05:56:45",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1692251805,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1691829313
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-08 06:29:14",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:33:56",
                    "question": "how much price veg brackfast, Lunch and dinner",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638944954,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952436,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18912085,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please advise if you will be staying or coming directly to the hotel.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 97,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:33:56"
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-06 08:38:01",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The room category have balcony with space to stand",
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 37223244,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686040681,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1686010541,
                    "question": "do the rooms have balconies?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-06 08:38:01",
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-06 00:15:41"
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 16656836,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "The Halfboard package includes breakfast and one major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival or lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:49:40",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-03 19:47:27",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:49:40",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "hi, all rooms show half board as lunch and breakfast but I want dinner and breakfast. will this be upgraded or adjusted on my check in?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1633290447,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351780
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Full board includes breakfast and two major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 95,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-20 14:02:46",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 13058832,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626540823,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626789766,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-17 16:53:43",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-20 14:02:46",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "What does full board meal include",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-02 05:22:34",
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The half board package includes breakfast and onemajor set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival or lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 18686608,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638422554,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638274936,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Half board means ?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-02 05:22:34",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-30 12:22:16"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 12256223,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The hotel offes a mix of European and Indian elegance, which is the architecture and design of the hotel and rooms.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:15:30",
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:15:30",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 07:35:50",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "room offer a mix of European and Indian elegance\n means...???",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625297750,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584530,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584378,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625332944,
                    "question": "What’s means full board meal",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:12:58",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 17:22:24",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": 93,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:12:58",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "The Full board package includes breakfast and two major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 12281710,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 36112455,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can offer twin bedded room, subject to availability. Suite category includes complimentary one way airport transfer.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-22 06:10:45",
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-22 06:10:45",
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-21 09:27:36",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello, can you swap a King Bed to 2 Twin Beds? \n\nDo you offer complimentary airport transfer? We are 6 Adults, and will visit for a week.\n\nThanks.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1682069256,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1682143845
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 91,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:49:00",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The same will be subject to availability on arrival.",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25291403,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654274940,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653904805,
                    "question": "How can I chose the floor number ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 10:00:05",
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:49:00"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 40903587,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answer": "We can offer interconnecting with one room City view and second room sea view, subject to availability on arrival",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-11-15 07:13:23",
                    "naive_sentiment": 89,
                    "answered_at": "2023-11-15 07:13:23",
                    "asked_at": "2023-11-13 04:22:05",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I'm travelling with my family (2 x adults and 2 x teenage children) arriving 8/12 and departing 11/12. Are you able to do interconnecting twin and double rooms. Can these be confirmed at the time of booking?\n",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1699849325,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1700032403
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:33:47",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-27 04:55:15",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "We are a family of 5 including a child of 12 yrs, kindly confirm if you  have interconnecting see facing rooms?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1609044915,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831627,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 6092843,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "In the Deluxe and Superior category we have interconnecting room sets that are subject to availability, with one being a sea view & the other a city view room.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 89,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:33:47"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-11-09 05:53:08",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:04:01",
                    "question": "How far from int’l airport?\nDo you have shuttle service airport pick up?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1667973188,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229441,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 32370574,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER CAR PER WAY):  (Rates are subject to change)\n\nOption I- Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n \nOption II- SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:04:01"
                },
                {
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 18352013,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-22 06:13:14",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in 1room. As there are 5 guests travelling, we would recommend 2rooms to be reserved.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "we are 5 members including 3 children's we need one room",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-22 06:13:14",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-19 14:38:20",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637561594,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1637332700
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 13415759,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:37:00",
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend 2 rooms to be reserved. You can book one city one sea in the Superior or Deluxe category, as we have ltd interconnecting sets",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello, I want to plan a staycation and we are family of 4 (kids - 11,14 yrs) is it possible to accomodate extra bed. And what charge for extra bed",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-24 09:22:14",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:37:00",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627231020,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627118534
                },
                {
                    "question": "ARRIVING 0300 ON 20TH AND DEPARTING ON 0800 AM ON 21ST \nSO HOW MANY DAYS HAS TO BE BOOKED ? AFTER LONG FLIGHT  I MUST GET ROOM WHEN ARRIVED NOT AT 1500 HRS \nPLEASE CLARIFY",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:12:12",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-08 23:09:17",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088332,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625785757,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 12593667,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 85,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:12:12",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do advise where you will be travelling from. The booking will need to be processed from the 19-20th to ensure a ready room on arrival."
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-10 07:07:34",
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-14 04:57:13",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "what will be the charge to the airport t2",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1686380854,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686718633,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 37324874,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-14 04:57:13",
                    "naive_sentiment": 83
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1662023733,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233643,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-09-01 09:15:33",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:14:03",
                    "question": "Hi is there an airport shuttle or are you close to the metro",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\n\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:14:03",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 30092625
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER WAY): (Rates are subject to change)\nOption Luxury Car:\nINR 8000/- plus 12% GST\nOption II - SUV:\nINR 4950/- plus 12% GST\n",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:27:53",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25513077,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654281949,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227273,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:27:53",
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-03 18:45:49",
                    "question": "Airport pickup charge?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "unmarried couples are allowed..?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:49:44",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-19 05:28:14",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570584,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632029294,
                    "question_id": 16112486,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:49:44",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes unmarried couples are allowed. Valid photo id proofs will be required at check-in."
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:11:29",
                    "naive_sentiment": 83,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The full board includes breakfast and two major set meal at a pre-designated venue. Please note the meal inclusion begins with dinner on the day of arrival and lunch on the day of check-out. High tea will be at an additional charge. Lounge is non-ope",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14810625,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465089,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629307720,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Full board includes which meals ?? High tea and lounge access included ??",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-18 17:28:40",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:11:29",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 81,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:49:57",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes you can",
                    "question_id": 33438024,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228597,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1672341617,
                    "question": "if i stay in tajmahal tower can i attend tajmahal palace resturant",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-12-29 19:20:17",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:49:57",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes you can ",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:49:35",
                    "naive_sentiment": 81,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 33438039,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1672341674,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228575,
                    "asked_at": "2022-12-29 19:21:14",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:49:35",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "if i stay in tajmahal tower can i visit resturant shamiana"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hello sir\nI'm married couples and one baby girl Age 10 old  to family room Available and lunch and Dinner extra pay ya  including for Booking",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:07:36",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-06 15:18:37",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040056,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628263117,
                    "question_id": 14162541,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 79,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:07:36",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "If I book with half board a superior room sea facing - will dinner be included for my kids aged 5 and 10",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:10:44",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-05 16:06:43",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584244,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625501203,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 12392599,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:10:44",
                    "naive_sentiment": 79,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 6921580,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly check the rates on the site",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:32:09",
                    "naive_sentiment": 79,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-05 10:15:55",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:32:09",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "One day package with food",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612520155,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539129
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2024-08-05 08:49:44",
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have sea view option in all room categories at Taj Mahal Tower",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 46563953,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1722847784,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1722509962,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Are there rooms with an ocean view ?",
                    "answered_at": "2024-08-05 08:49:44",
                    "asked_at": "2024-08-01 10:59:22",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:14:53",
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes. Kindly request for the same when processing the booking.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 12522770,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088493,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625683498,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, do you have smoking rooms available?",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:14:53",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-07 18:44:58",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613137168,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612969256,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do u have a facilities for airport drop ?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-10 15:00:56",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-12 13:39:28",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-12 13:39:28",
                    "naive_sentiment": 75,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The smae will be at an addittional charge. Kindly do request the same directly from the booking.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 7051694,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 15097147,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 73,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:55:42",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Yes unmarried couples are allowed. A valid photo id proofs will be required per guest at the time of check-in.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "unmarried couple allow this hotel",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-24 19:16:53",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:55:42",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899742,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629832613
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607802015,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051503,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-12 19:40:15",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 16:58:23",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "its my dream stay 1 day at Taj hotel.but the check in timing and checkout timing are 20th december  night 11pm to 21st december 11.pm .  sea facing",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. For a late check-out at 23:00 hrs the room wil need booked till the 22nd December.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 16:58:23",
                    "naive_sentiment": 73,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 5849973
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I want room for 24 hrs price ??",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-23 09:35:01",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:53:48",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899628,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629711301,
                    "question_id": 15021249,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:53:48",
                    "naive_sentiment": 71,
                    "answer": "Kindly view the rates online. Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12777378,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 71,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-14 16:06:57",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do refer to the web site for the details for the same.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "kindly let us know your charges for breakfast + dinner on 30/07 and 31/07/2021 along with accomodation charges for superior sea view room for 2 pax",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-12 16:02:34",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-14 16:06:57",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626278817,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626105754
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229471,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1668090766,
                    "question": "Does the hotel offers a clock room facility  to keep the baggage for early arrival guests ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-11-10 14:32:46",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:04:31",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:04:31",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "You can leave the bags with the bell desk till the check in",
                    "question_id": 32411423,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 24830490,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:06:12",
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. We recommend to adhere by the standard timings.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "How many hours check out time",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:06:12",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-20 09:42:50",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653843972,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653039770
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 17728534,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answer": "The airport transfer can be arranged at charge. Kindly do write to us directly from the messaging option on your booking.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:43:30",
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:43:30",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-01 20:26:08",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do you have shuttle service from Mumbai Airport",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1635798368,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907410,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1617966603,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1617966743,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-09 11:12:23",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-09 11:10:03",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Pool access available?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "In light of the current situation, we have implemented enhanced precautionary hygiene measures across our hotel. As per government advisories, certain services, including Swimming Pool are non-operational.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 69,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-09 11:12:23",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 8690402,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660123465,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233780,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:16:20",
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-10 09:24:25",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "What is checking in and out time",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. ",
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:16:20",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 29081704,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:28:15",
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. ",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 25624226,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227295,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654500250,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "What is the Check in time",
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-06 07:24:10",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:28:15",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 21137316,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:25:45",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Are check out time flexible ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-13 13:36:36",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:25:45",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827145,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644759396
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628243040,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040027,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:07:07",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-06 09:44:00",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "What is the policy for children",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. Children above 12 years are considered as adults. Children up to 12 years of age will be entitled to a free stay in the existing bedding on room only basis. ",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:07:07",
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 14146430
                },
                {
                    "question": "check in time?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:11:19",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-03 06:33:40",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176279,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627972420,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 13962500,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:11:19",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs."
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621694753,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621840388,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-24 07:13:08",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-22 14:45:53",
                    "question": "Timing check in check out",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-24 07:13:08",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 10197596
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422639,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607275921,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "check in time & check out time",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:17:19",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-06 17:32:01",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:17:19",
                    "naive_sentiment": 67,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 5740522,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 25257175,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please check the site for the available tarrifs.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:56",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:56",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-29 15:47:10",
                    "question": "Breakfast and dinner with room tariff",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653839230,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653844076,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, I am visiting 31st March and 15th April. I would like to book 2 rooms with 3 occupants each, is it possible to add an extra kids bed in each room?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-03 08:22:19",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:32:49",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952369,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638519739,
                    "question_id": 18771542,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:32:49",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. One Child up to 12 years of age will be entitled to a free stay in the existing bedding on room only basis. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs.  For the late check-out at 23:00 hrs an additional full day's charge will be applicable.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 16:57:31",
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 5844398,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607779628,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051451,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 16:57:31",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-12 13:27:08",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "i want a room but the check in timing and chect oot timing is from 11.pm to 11.pm\nfor 1 day  seaview in taj"
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Yes we can accomodate unmarried couples",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 65,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-24 12:29:39",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 4652438,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1599990695,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1603542579,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-13 09:51:35",
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-24 12:29:39",
                    "question": "Are unmarried couples allowed for accommodation",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 14270561,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answer": "Superior rooms are located between the 3rd-10th floor while Deluxe rooms are located between the 11-19th floor.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:08:18",
                    "naive_sentiment": 63,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:08:18",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-08 17:43:12",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "what's the difference between superior room and deluxe room?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628444592,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040098,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 14153465,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:07:19",
                    "naive_sentiment": 61,
                    "answer": "Yes int he room only.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is outside alcohol allowed?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-06 12:11:58",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:07:19",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040039,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628251918
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831973,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613653584,
                    "question": "hii. can we accomadate an extra person in our room since my mother will be accompanying us. 3 adults and 1 child.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:39:33",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-18 13:06:24",
                    "naive_sentiment": 61,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:39:33",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests in one room including children.",
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 7263220,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618551020,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619083400,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-16 05:30:20",
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-22 09:23:20",
                    "question": "Unmarried  couples  (lover's) are allowed or not?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, Unmarried couple's are allowed as long as the valid photo id proofs are shared.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 59,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-22 09:23:20",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8889225
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-12 13:39:52",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-11 15:25:34",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is swimming pool working?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613057134,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613137192,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 7080228,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently non-operational.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 59,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-12 13:39:52"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is there any charge for swimming pool",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-01 05:28:59",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:12:07",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422327,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1572586139,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 1534037,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 59,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:12:07",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently non-operational."
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 57,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-10-17 04:05:23",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Daily breakfast will be served between 7:00 hrs. to 10:30hrs at a pre-designated dining venue\n• Meal service timings are mentioned as below:\no Lunch: 12:30hrs to 15:00hrs\no Dinner: 19:00hrs to 23:30hrs",
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 39823902,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1697515523,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1695165692,
                    "question": "What are the timing for breakfast and dinner?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-10-17 04:05:23",
                    "asked_at": "2023-09-19 23:21:32"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621840431,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621803181,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "How many persons can accommodate in a room??",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-23 20:53:01",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-24 07:13:51",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-24 07:13:51",
                    "naive_sentiment": 57,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests in total in a room including children.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 10253496,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 24646429,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We can arrnage for the interconnecting set in the Superior and Deluxe category with one room being a sea view adn the other a city view. However the rooms are limited. The City view room room will be a twin bedded room.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 55,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 12:59:25",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-16 14:36:57",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 12:59:25",
                    "question": "We want two rooms with connected door and separately bed",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652711817,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792365,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:23:41",
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-13 09:59:09",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello,  as we have the room with dinner option, which restaurants should be available for us? What will be the dinner options?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644746349,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827021,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 21129741,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The breakfast and one major set meal at a pre-designated venue will be at the All day dining restaurant the Shamiana.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:23:41",
                    "naive_sentiment": 55
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is swimming pool operational?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-09 17:26:48",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-10 08:30:31",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633854631,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1633800408,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question_id": 16876687,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-10 08:30:31",
                    "naive_sentiment": 53,
                    "answer": "In light of the current situation, we have implemented enhanced precautionary hygiene measures across our hotel. As per government advisories, certain services, likeSwimming Pool, is non-operational.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621364661,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621753514,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-23 07:05:14",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-18 19:04:21",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Cant we decorate the room for birthday celebration",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The same can be aanged at charge. Kindly do write to us directly from the booking confirmation. ",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-23 07:05:14",
                    "naive_sentiment": 53,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 10038976,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 14894081,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Subject to room availability. Kindly place the request directly from your room booking.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:13:08",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:13:08",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-20 10:37:32",
                    "question": "Planning to book for 21-22 aug, 2 rooms 4 adults . Early check in possible ??",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629455852,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465188,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:11:01",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. ",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 14049202,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176261,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628090807,
                    "question": "Hi m planing to visit the Taj Mahal palace with my mom my sis me my wife & my 8 yrs old son.what kind of room would u suggest me.\nAlso the room rate.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-04 15:26:47",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:11:01"
                },
                {
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13436077,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:35:43",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. ",
                    "question": "What are best offers for family of four for one day including all meals. We can stay in one room also",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-24 17:08:05",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:35:43",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627230943,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627146485
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 13159878,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "As per government advisories, certain services, including Swimming Pool, may be non-operational. The health and safety of our guests and associates is our utmost priority and we look forward to welcoming you at the hotel.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-20 14:02:22",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-20 14:02:22",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-19 15:23:34",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hi is the pool functional?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626708214,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626789742
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-15 15:45:04",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-15 15:01:34",
                    "question": "Can 4 guests occupy a single room",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626361294,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626363904,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 12950563,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-15 15:45:04"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "If the booking is made on triple occupancy on the package that includes Breakfast lunch and dinner then the meals are applicable for all three guests.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-07 05:28:25",
                    "naive_sentiment": 47,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 8543925,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1617539472,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1617773305,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-07 05:28:25",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-04 12:31:12",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does Breakfast lunch and dinner is applicable for all 3 peoples."
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627231055,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627038774,
                    "question": "Would like to stay in the palace wing of this iconic hotel on my first ever trip to Mumbai from 30th July to 1st August.Please help .",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:37:35",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-23 11:12:54",
                    "naive_sentiment": 45,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:37:35",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly check the available packages on the site",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13372145,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do request for a smoking room.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 45,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-11-04 19:16:09",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 5315034,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1604412659,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1604517369,
                    "answered_at": "2020-11-04 19:16:09",
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-03 14:10:59",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is smoking allowed in the balcony?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:02:19",
                    "asked_at": "2022-12-06 10:43:14",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I will be travelling to India with my husband, 10 month baby and currently pregnant. Will I be able to check in earlier around 1pm?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1670323394,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229339,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 32994805,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The same can be confirmed, subject to availability, on arrival",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:02:19",
                    "naive_sentiment": 43
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Thank you for your interest. We needed some additional details regarding your requirement to be able to respond to your query.   ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-09-18 13:44:28",
                    "naive_sentiment": 43,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 4723892,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1600435889,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1600436668,
                    "answered_at": "2020-09-18 13:44:28",
                    "asked_at": "2020-09-18 13:31:29",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is it the collest hotle of mumbai?"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kindly refer to the web site for applicable rates.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:13:14",
                    "naive_sentiment": 41,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 14486040,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628769238,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040394,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-12 11:53:58",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:13:14",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "If I want to include Dinner also during my stay for 3 nights then what would be charges total"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1681342922,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1681360362,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-13 04:32:42",
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-12 23:42:02",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do you provide Twin rooms? I am looking at booking a hotel in Mumbai for x6 adults (males) but can’t seem to find any options to book twin rooms?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Superior Room City view and Deluxe room city view have twin bedded room, subject to availability",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-13 04:32:42",
                    "naive_sentiment": 39,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 35903187
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 18:03:22",
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:52:18",
                    "question": "Hello ,\n\nWe are a family of 4 person and i would like to get 1 room,is that possible? 2 adult 2 teenagers.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653933802,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275138,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25314364,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. Children above 12 years are considered as adults. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 37,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:52:18"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:14:39",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-08 15:59:42",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hi. we are family of 4, 2 adults and 2 k8ds age 9 and 14 yrs. we want half board package, what booking option should we take",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625759982,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088479,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 12570867,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. As there are 4 guests travelling, we would recommend two rooms to be reserved. Children above 12 years are considered as adults. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": 37,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:14:39"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608051382,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607883083,
                    "question": "Is there any charges for jacuzzi????",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-13 18:11:23",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-15 16:56:22",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": 33,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-15 16:56:22",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly note the room category booked only has a walk-in shower.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 5866078,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "we are  coming from gulf . planning to stay here for one day.Can we call relatives to meet us .If yes how many members can meet and what is the time .",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-01 19:30:25",
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:54:01",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275241,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654111825,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 25419978,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:54:01",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Maximum of 4 guests can meeat in a room and the visitor timings are from 09:00-20:00 hrs. Incase there are more guests you can meet them in one of the restaurants with a prior table reservation."
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:09:46",
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly write to us from the message option on your booking for the Celebrations menu.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14688392,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629464986,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629120336,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "It’s my husbands birthday on the 24th .., can you do something special for him",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:09:46",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-16 13:25:36",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626278844,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626111182,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, \nDo I get a balcony in my room?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-12 17:33:02",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-14 16:07:24",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-14 16:07:24",
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in whicha  guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 12782524,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-14 16:20:38",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-14 15:01:14",
                    "question": "Hi\nWhat do you mean by FULL BOARD included?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621004474,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621009238,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 9864650,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Full board would mean the room rate is inclusive of all meals (breakfast, lunch and dinner)",
                    "naive_sentiment": 31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-14 16:20:38"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621629191,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621753467,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-21 20:33:11",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-23 07:04:27",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi .Is the pool and spa operational or its closed due to Covid.Also If I book a Full board meal,Is it on Al Al a Carte or it is vast spread buffet.",
                    "answer": "TH ehotel is operational as per gvernment restrictions. The Full board meals is a set meal ofered at the All Day dining restaurant Shamiana.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-23 07:04:27",
                    "naive_sentiment": 29,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 10172802
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 5748024,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answer": "The meal in the package that includes meals is served at a pre-designated dining venue. If the package includes hotel credit then that credit can be used against In room dining food orders.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:16:38",
                    "naive_sentiment": 29,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-07 03:26:22",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:16:38",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "If we book for an inclusive dinner will it be served in the room ?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607311582,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422598,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1583089763,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1583392837,
                    "asked_at": "2020-03-01 19:09:23",
                    "answered_at": "2020-03-05 07:20:37",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "I only want dinner can i book a table",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We would request you to kindly contact Our Food & Beverages team on the hotel contact number mentioned on the Taj hotel contact details so that they can assist you with the applicable options. ",
                    "naive_sentiment": 29,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-03-05 07:20:37",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 2729807,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 17360389,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:42:09",
                    "naive_sentiment": 25,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. The third occupant would be charged INR. 3000+18% taxes.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi I want to stay at your Hotel if I brings an other person till date not final then what is you extra Bed Charges",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:42:09",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-22 16:22:08",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907329,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634919728
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351618,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632737465,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, will the Deluxe and Superior sea view rooms both have a view of the ocean and the Gateway? What is the difference between these two rooms?",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:46:58",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-27 10:11:05",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:46:58",
                    "naive_sentiment": 25,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Superior Sea view rooms are located between the 3rd-10th floors while the Deluxe Sea view rooms are located between the 11th-19th floors. They both have Sea view. The higher the floors the more birds eye view of the Gateway Of India is viewable.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 16417905,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-30 11:49:29",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:27:01",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Smoking arrangements",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1656589769,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234421,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 26864057,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The hotel has the options of smoking & non-smoking accommodation",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:27:01",
                    "naive_sentiment": 23
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 18920348,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 23,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:17:49",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We can note the request for the early check-in however we are unable to confirm the same. Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "We want to check in before time 12 pm on 17 December is it possible",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:17:49",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-08 12:48:06",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138669,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638967686
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 15952945,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 23,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:22:41",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Subject to availability. Kindly note the Standard check-in time of the hotel is 15:00 hrs and the standard checkout time is 11:00 hrs. In case the room is not ready  you can leave your baggage at the Bell Desk and check in later.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Hii i have booked room, according to my flight time i will reach around 9:30. Can we do early check in",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:22:41",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-14 19:05:07",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712161,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631646307
                },
                {
                    "question": "hi could we request an extra bed for 3rd adult",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-21 23:23:48",
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-22 06:09:17",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1682143757,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1682119428,
                    "question_id": 36127910,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-22 06:09:17",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can arrange for an extra bed at INR 3000+taxes per night"
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:15:09",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests including children in one room. Two rooms will need to be booked.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 22872877,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830509,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649012453,
                    "question": "Do you have any options that can accommodate 4 guests in a room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-03 19:00:53",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:15:09"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632656102,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351132,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-26 11:35:02",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:38:52",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "i want inter connected room",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please place the request directly on your booking chat service.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:38:52",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 16383495,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 9024565,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-22 09:25:53",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, if you do select the set meal package with all meals, the same is at the All day dining restaurant Shamiana and will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per guest booked. ",
                    "question": "Is sea lounge access included in the all meal package?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-22 09:25:53",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-20 17:27:38",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619083553,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618939658
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-07 05:51:11",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:33:26",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Dear sir / Madam\nMy name is Virendra Kewadkar from Aurangabad,\nthere is no any Flexible time for check in at 8.00 in the morning.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638856271,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952406,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 18881299,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can offer an early check in at 08:00 am at additional half day charge. Kindly advise in case you wish to avail the same.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 19,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:33:26"
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 26201721,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "You can carry one liquor bottle for consumption in the room",
                    "naive_sentiment": 17,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:38:33",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:38:33",
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-17 16:10:17",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is own liquor bottles allowed?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1655482217,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227913
                },
                {
                    "answer": "The set meal at Shamiana will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:06:00",
                    "naive_sentiment": 17,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 13656833,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627487273,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905960,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-28 15:47:53",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:06:00",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Half Board includes breakfast and dinner at any restaurant of your choice or ?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "hi, is there complimentary breakfast",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-31 13:12:21",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-28 17:03:47",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1630415541,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630170227,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 15265331,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 15,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-31 13:12:21",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Depends on the package booked"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "\n\nDear Sir,\n \nGreetings from the Taj.\n\n\n\nFurther to the below email, vaccination certificate is not compulsory.  You can fill the health declaration form on arrival.\n\nRegards,\n\nKrishin\nReservations",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-07 09:26:35",
                    "naive_sentiment": 15,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 14192352,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628321989,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628328395,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-07 07:39:49",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-07 09:26:35",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "is vaccine certification is compulsory? I m planning to book for 2 tomorrow"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627658605,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905909,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-30 15:23:25",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:05:09",
                    "question": "is there any conditions for 60 above bcz of ds covid situation",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Individuals with a cough, cold, or a temperature of more than 98.6F or 37.3C will regrettably not be permitted entry into the hotel premises for the safety and security of all concerned. ",
                    "naive_sentiment": 15,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:05:09",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 13767433
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18410162,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-22 06:13:36",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in which a guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "question": "Is balcony attached to every rooms?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-22 06:13:36",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-21 14:23:19",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637561616,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1637504599
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712094,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631683074,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "does it have a standing balcony?",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:21:34",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-15 05:17:54",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:21:34",
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note the Superior and Deluxe rooms and Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai have French windows that open into a balcony in which a guest can comfortably stand in.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 15967274,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:04:02",
                    "naive_sentiment": 13,
                    "answer": "Please check the available packages on the site.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 13770414,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905842,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627662218,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "include dinner",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:04:02",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-30 16:23:38",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:43:02",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-27 01:17:48",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "For pool and towel we have to give additional charge \nOr it is in the price of room only",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632705468,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351382,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 16409236,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The pool service is currently non-operational. The health and safety of our guests and associates is our utmost priority and we look forward to welcoming you at the hotel. Towels are provided in the room.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 11,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:43:02"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627211109,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627230917,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-25 11:05:09",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:35:17",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "What food included for this booking",
                    "answer": "Kindly check the package booked",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:35:17",
                    "naive_sentiment": 11,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 13466840,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We accept credit cards.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 9,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-18 11:01:35",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 15999192,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631741614,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631962895,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-18 11:01:35",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-15 21:33:34",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Do you accept HDFC Bank Diners Credit Card",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please do check the webite for details fo the same.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:13:14",
                    "naive_sentiment": 9,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 12268875,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625316861,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584394,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:13:14",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 12:54:21",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "All meal charges pl"
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 40378509,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "As per hotel policy, we can accommodate maximum 3 guests in a room (including children). In event of 4 guests, 2 rooms must be booked.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-10-17 04:08:15",
                    "asked_at": "2023-10-16 16:44:14",
                    "answered_at": "2023-10-17 04:08:15",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hello, we have two children and my husband and I would all like to be in the same room. Is this possible as it’s saying we need 2 separate rooms?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1697474654,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1697515695
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-01-05 12:51:00",
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please refere to the rates available online. Once booked we can share the various celebrations packages available.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 19717307,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1641387060,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641385763,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "hi how do we book honeymoon suite",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-01-05 12:51:00",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-05 12:29:23"
                },
                {
                    "question": "food is included in the stay price or not",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-15 17:48:28",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:58:30",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599110,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639590508,
                    "question_id": 19137456,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:58:30",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please check the rate description it will advise whats included in the package."
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599052,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639314459,
                    "question": "Hi\nBreakfast included in this rate ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-12 13:07:39",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:57:32",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:57:32",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Please check the rate description.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 19033110,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:57:20",
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "answer": "A seperate room will need to be booked as available online.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 18989388,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599040,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639163015,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "can driver stay there ?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-10 19:03:35",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:57:20",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": 7,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:11:57",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Please refer to the online rates fot the same",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 14863106,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465117,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629393556,
                    "question": "We want breakfast and Dinner package too",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-19 17:19:16",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:11:57"
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "There are showr blinds which can be lowered.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:52:46",
                    "naive_sentiment": 5,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 25320098,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653940083,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275166,
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 19:48:03",
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:52:46",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I have noticed from the room picture that the shower room is exposed, is there any curtains or a way to cover it?"
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 9653772,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:15:53",
                    "naive_sentiment": 5,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes we hvae Jain food available. While the booking is being processed please share your preference for Jain food.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "if we book with full board, is thier jain food avaible",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-09 07:21:43",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:15:53",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354553,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620544903
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 7586849,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 5,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:44:59",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The GST depends on your room rate.",
                    "question": "Hi this amount included GSt",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:44:59",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-02 14:34:38",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951899,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614695678
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 23105959,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:14:01",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Yes fully vaccinated guests  or guests with RTPCR of 48 hours prior will be accepted.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Are only vaccinated travelers from COVID-19 allowed to stay at the hotel?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-09 17:42:45",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:14:01",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830441,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649526165
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:13:47",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-08 17:02:20",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "if i take a half board package and take an additional bed at rs 3000 for my 14 year old kid, will she be included in half board package?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625763740,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088427,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 12574191,
                    "answer": "We have a maximum occupancy of 3 guests in a room including children. Children above 12 are considered as adults. If the booking is processed on triple occupancy basis it will include the extra bed and meals as per the package booked.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:13:47",
                    "naive_sentiment": 3
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621935490,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584119,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:08:39",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-25 09:38:10",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does one have to pay extra charges for child meal even if the plan opted is full board for 2 adults and 1 kid",
                    "answer": "The meal is only inclusive for the adults booked. There is a child supplement charge applicable fo rhte meals of the child.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:08:39",
                    "naive_sentiment": 3,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 10319376,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830521,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1648972022,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is brekfast including this prices?",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-03 07:47:02",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:15:21",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:15:21",
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "answer": "Please check the inclusions in your package.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 22848250,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 16496414,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Depends on the package selected.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:47:19",
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-29 09:38:58",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:47:19",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "is lunch, dinner and BF included?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632908338,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351639
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:12:41",
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please refere to the inclusions of the package booked. If booked a package inclsuive of set meals. The set meal at Shamiana will include one starter, one main course and one dessert per adult guest booked.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14888180,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465161,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629446397,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is the dinner included in package a buffet or set menu?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-20 07:59:57",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:12:41",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040370,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628764200,
                    "question": "Are there any new Covid-19 norms regarding stays at hotels and restaurants. Also which floor does the deluxe sea view room starts.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-12 10:30:00",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:12:50",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:12:50",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly as the chat space is limited. Deluxe rooms are located between the 11-19th floor.",
                    "question_id": 14481962,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 5740564,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes. Please ensure you mention the preference for Jain food in your reservation.",
                    "naive_sentiment": 1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:17:04",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-06 17:34:02",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:17:04",
                    "question": "is Jain food available?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607276042,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422624,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 19178572,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -1,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:58:05",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Each hotel has a different policy.",
                    "question": "Why it is confined to only one starter, main course and one desert in full board  Rest of the properties have a buffet in one of their restaurant",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:58:05",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-17 05:11:49",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599085,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639717909
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Apollo Suite category only have bathtub",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-05-05 06:42:53",
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 36438930,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1683191318,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1683268973,
                    "answered_at": "2023-05-05 06:42:53",
                    "asked_at": "2023-05-04 09:08:38",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there bathtub in sea view room?"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1680345929,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1680419243,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2023-04-01 10:45:29",
                    "answered_at": "2023-04-02 07:07:23",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, just wanted to confirm that the bathroom\nwith this room is not shared? In the booking overview, it is says that it is a room with shared bathroom.",
                    "answer": "The room has a bathroom with toilet and shower cubicle",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-04-02 07:07:23",
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question_id": 35626761
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:10:11",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-10 15:58:45",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "unmarried couples allowed?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625932725,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088211,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 12673386,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Yes, both guests will need to carry valid photo id proof.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:10:11"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 7156064,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answer": "Kindly process the booking on triple occupancy if three guests are travelling.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:40:48",
                    "naive_sentiment": -3,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:40:48",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-14 16:08:22",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "for extra person there is any charges",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613318902,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613832048
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 16114228,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -5,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:50:29",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "If the booking is made on triple occupancy an extra bed will be provided for the third guest. Kindly do send us the request directly from your booking.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Is it there an extra bed for the third guest in the superior sea facing room....as we are 3 adults?..secondly, it's my daughter's birthday can I order a cake....can the hotel help me with it..?  Last but not the least, which restaurants are there in the hotel  premises?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-19 07:38:56",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:50:29",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570629,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632037136
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 35596920,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-31 08:33:18",
                    "naive_sentiment": -7,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "As per hotel policy, maximum 3 guests in a room (including children).  In event of 4 guests, 2 rooms must be booked.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "My family including my wife, 9 year old baby boy and 5 year old a baby girl. Is it possible that we will stay together in one room.",
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-31 01:53:27",
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-31 08:33:18",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1680251598,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1680227607
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 1662078,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please be informed that lunch and dinner will be served on Al A Carte.\nRequest you to advise your booking confirmation number in order to advise your further",
                    "naive_sentiment": -7,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2019-11-20 09:26:49",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2019-11-18 08:18:39",
                    "answered_at": "2019-11-20 09:26:49",
                    "question": "WE need to include lunch & dinner in the package",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1574065119,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1574242009,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1654275065,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653925692,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi in this three adult and one children of 14 years half bording charges are included?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-06-03 16:51:05",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-30 15:48:12",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-06-03 16:51:05",
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "answer": "2 separate rooms will need to be booked as we have a maximum of 3 guests in 1 room including children. Over 12 yrs are considered as adults. Rates As per the available package online. Children above 5-12 yrs will be charged additional for the meals.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 25307607,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-16 09:07:36",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 12:59:54",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, purpose of travel is to celebrate my 20th marriage Anniversari, do u have any special offer for such event.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652692056,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792394,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 24631972,
                    "answer": "We can make arrangements for your special occassion at an additional charge. Kindly contact the hotel directly.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 12:59:54",
                    "naive_sentiment": -9
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:15:37",
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes charges apply.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 22848124,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830537,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1648971617,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Minibar is chargeable?",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:15:37",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-03 07:40:17",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 15621729,
                    "answer": "Depends on the package booked. Please write directly from the booking made.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:23:31",
                    "naive_sentiment": -9,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-06 11:47:07",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:23:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I want to know cancellation policy of Taj hotels",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630928827,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712211,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:46:23",
                    "naive_sentiment": -11,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Complimentary standard wi-fi for 4 devices is available.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 6398385,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887583,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610339795,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "is wifi available in rooms ? if yes is it free or chargeable",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:46:23",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-11 04:36:35",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634654436,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907267,
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-19 14:40:36",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:41:07",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Do you provide an extra bed on request for an extra person",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "If the booking is on double occupancy you can amend the same to triple occupancy and an extra bed will be provided automatically for the third guest.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -13,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:41:07",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 17239775,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes you may book for 16th July now.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-01 15:58:37",
                    "naive_sentiment": -13,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 10647083,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1622562727,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1622563117,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-01 15:52:07",
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-01 15:58:37",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Wish to book 1 night stay on  July 16. We are residing in Mumbai and haven’t travelled abroad in last few years. Is it possible to book now?"
                },
                {
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 6900441,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:35:12",
                    "naive_sentiment": -13,
                    "answer": "Set meal menu ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Lunch & Dinner included are buffet????",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-04 10:49:13",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:35:12",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539312,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612435753
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1617773339,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616953548,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there a swimming pool and is it functional",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-28 17:45:48",
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-07 05:28:59",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-07 05:28:59",
                    "naive_sentiment": -15,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "As per government advisories, certain services, including but not limited to spa, salon, Swimming Pool, fitness center, may be non-operational. The health and safety of our guests and associates is our utmost priority.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 8358537,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1637007376,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137510,
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:25:10",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-15 20:16:16",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "hi I am traveling with my parents my check-in time ll be 5pm ,can I get 24hrs fr my check out.",
                    "answer": "We can offer a confirmed late check-out by 17:00 hrs at an additional quarter days charge plus taxes.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:25:10",
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 18224318,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040133,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628447631,
                    "question": "Is there a poo",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-08 18:33:51",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:08:53",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:08:53",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Pool services are currently non operational.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 14273459,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:13:44",
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "answer": "Please check the wesite for details for the same according to your stay dates.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 12268727,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584424,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625316646,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "How much extra for all meals.",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-03 12:50:46",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:13:44",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:34:45",
                    "naive_sentiment": -19,
                    "answer": "We do allow couples",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 6916859,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539285,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612495581,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi... is this hotel couple friendly..",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-05 03:26:21",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:34:45",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 20348320,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President - IHCL Seleqtions, is a pet friendly hotel in case you wish to travel with your companion ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:12:15",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:12:15",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-23 13:56:40",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hi I am traveling with my pet. Will you allow it?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642946200,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830335
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-10-04 12:40:21",
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "answer": "The Taj Mahal Tower is the modern hotel while the Taj Mahal Palace is the Heritage hotel. It would depend on the hotel you choose to book at. The pool service is non-operational.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 16403045,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1633351221,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632689381,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "how do u differentiate between Tower & palace rooms? how would I know prior check in where am I going to get placed? is swimming pool operational now?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-26 20:49:41",
                    "answered_at": "2021-10-04 12:40:21",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is this a pet friendly hotel",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-13 11:06:16",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:13:34",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040414,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628852776,
                    "question_id": 14538035,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:13:34",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President - IHCL Seleqtions, is a pet friendly hotel in case you wish to travel with your companion"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608300286,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1608389314,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-19 14:48:34",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-18 14:04:46",
                    "question": "Is there is a bath tub in the room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "There is only a walk in shower in the Superior and Deluxe room category. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite at the Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and in the rooms and suites at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Kindly place a request for the same.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-19 14:48:34",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 5954398
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 5527871,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "In line with the hotel policy, pets are not allowed at the hotel. Our sister property, President - IHCL Seleqtions, is a pet friendly hotel in case you wish to travel with your companion.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -21,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-11-22 21:57:23",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2020-11-22 21:57:23",
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-21 13:52:16",
                    "question": "Hi Team,\n\nThis is Yogesh here. I want planning book a suite with my wife and my pet Solo (a pug). Heard that our property is a pet friendly property.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1605966736,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1606082243,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636688022,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137453,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-12 03:33:42",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:24:13",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "contact details",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please do check the same on the taj Hotels web site as we are unable to share contact details on the chat service.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:24:13",
                    "naive_sentiment": -23,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 18095848,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 13703791,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -23,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:05:37",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Yes its on an A La Carte basis.",
                    "question": "Are there charges levied on products consumed from the minibar?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-29 12:24:57",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:05:37",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905937,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627561497
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 17927084,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "N2 non resident guests can certainly visit. Kindly contact the duty manager for the same. Outside cake would be allowed in the room only.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-08 08:32:41",
                    "naive_sentiment": -25,
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-07 15:42:14",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-08 08:32:41",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, can you bring 2 local resident guest during stay for an hour? Also, is outside customized birthday cake allowed in room ?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636299734,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1636360361
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827063,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644722518,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do you provide drivers accommodations?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:24:23",
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-13 03:21:58",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:24:23",
                    "naive_sentiment": -27,
                    "answer": "A seperate room reservation will need to be processed for the driver.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 21123054,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138706,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639132520,
                    "question": "Are your swimming pools operational?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:18:26",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-10 10:35:20",
                    "naive_sentiment": -27,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:18:26",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Current guidelines in Maharashtra do not permit the usage of the swimming pool. Keeping this in mind, the hotel is in the process of upgrading our product.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 18977074,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Payment can be made by credit card.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -27,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:50:43",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 16132067,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632069965,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570643,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:50:43",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-19 16:46:05",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Can we do payment by credit card?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-07 09:38:00",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:14:43",
                    "question": "hi can we carry our own liquor to room , I mean if we can consume in our room ....",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649324280,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830483,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 23014384,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Outsice alcohol can be consumed in the room only.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:14:43"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 19961864,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "answer": "Half board includes breakfast and one major set meal at a pre-designated venue.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:22:58",
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:22:58",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-12 14:44:50",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Half board included means",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641998690,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644826978,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354507,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621323300,
                    "question": "Hello, does this superior room has bathtub?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:15:07",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-18 07:35:00",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:15:07",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walkin shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 10012086,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Hie is there a bath tub in the room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:14:21",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-09 06:45:39",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354461,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620542739,
                    "question_id": 9653299,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:14:21",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walkin shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 6342418,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -29,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-09 13:46:08",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-09 13:46:08",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-08 07:16:41",
                    "question": "Do you have bath tub ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610090201,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610199968,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1685993191,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1686040611,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-06 08:36:51",
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-05 19:26:31",
                    "question": "hi \ndo you have a driver to pick me up from the airport?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "AIRPORT TRANSFER CHARGES (PER CAR PER WAY):  (Rates are subject to change) - SUV: INR 4950/- plus 12% GST\nThe flight details and guest contact number in case the airport transfers needs to be arranged (minimum 24 hours prior intimation is needed). \n",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-06 08:36:51",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 37218369
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653068215,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653843993,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-20 17:36:55",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:06:33",
                    "question": "Hi are there bath tubs cause I cannot see it in the pictures and also can we get our own alcohol bottles ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:06:33",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 24849072
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641911567,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830218,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:10:18",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-11 14:32:47",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "does every room have bathtub ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:10:18",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 19924862,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:31:58",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "question_id": 18750432,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952318,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638453559,
                    "question": "hi do we have bath tub in all the rooms",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:31:58",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-02 13:59:19",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636659299,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1636796998,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-13 09:49:58",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-11 19:34:59",
                    "question": "is there a bathtub",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-13 09:49:58",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 18085760
                },
                {
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 17408906,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:42:27",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question": "Which sea facing rooms have bathtub facility?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:42:27",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-24 02:34:32",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907347,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1635042872
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1634470539,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907224,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:40:24",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-17 11:35:39",
                    "question": "Does this room come with bath tub",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:40:24",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 17153271
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1632570658,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1632167361,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does superior room has a bath tub",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-20 19:49:21",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-25 11:50:58",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-25 11:50:58",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 16178465,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "Is bathtub available in taj mahal tower superior city view room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-31 13:12:36",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-31 05:30:37",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1630415556,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630387837,
                    "question_id": 15367515,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-31 13:12:36",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai."
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629218500,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629464953,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:09:13",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-17 16:41:40",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "does this room have bath tub ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:09:13",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 14753793,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629049560,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629464946,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-15 17:46:00",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:09:06",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi. Do you have bathtub?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:09:06",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 14650520,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I want a bath tub",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:09:39",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-02 15:08:09",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176179,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627916889,
                    "question_id": 13926703,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:09:39",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 13413722,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:37:15",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi do you have a bathtub in superior room",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-24 08:22:00",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:37:15",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627231035,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627114920
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 13476182,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-25 16:35:07",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "is there a bath tub",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-25 14:10:00",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-25 16:35:07",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627230907,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627222200
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 13176619,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-20 14:01:52",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-20 14:01:52",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-19 20:16:49",
                    "question": "does this rooms have bathtub?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626725809,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626789712,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626527698,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626531969,
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-17 14:26:09",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-17 13:14:58",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is there a bathtub available",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-17 14:26:09",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 13048479,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-14 16:07:50",
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-07 02:22:21",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does the room have a bath tub",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1623032541,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626278870,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 10911078,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-14 16:07:50",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:11:35",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 12351667,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625433077,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584295,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:11:35",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-04 21:11:17",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, do you have bathtub in this room ?"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-29 19:34:33",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-06 15:09:31",
                    "question": "Do all the rooms have tubs in the bathroom",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1622316873,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1625584171,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 10519913,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-06 15:09:31"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-06-22 17:53:11",
                    "answered_at": "2021-06-24 05:36:39",
                    "question": "Hey I need a room with bathtub & smoking in room is okay?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1624384391,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1624512999,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 11696137,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. ",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-06-24 05:36:39"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-25 16:24:24",
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-26 04:11:57",
                    "question": "will every room have a bathtub. where can I check if not",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1619367864,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1619410317,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 9177537,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room categories at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walki-n shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-26 04:11:57"
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8730665,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room categories at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-11 06:49:04",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-10 21:33:01",
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-11 06:49:04",
                    "question": "Hi, do your rooms have a bath tub?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618090381,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1618123744,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 6493161,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-17 12:45:54",
                    "naive_sentiment": -31,
                    "answer": "Two seperate rooms will need to be reserved as we have a maximum occupancy of three guest including children. Children twelve years and above are considered as adults. Once the booking has been processed the required information will be shared ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Me n my husband wish to visit with our 2 daughter, age 14 n 9, so can we accommodate in one single room, what will be the price. And to book a room what documents are needed. As we live in Thane, Maharashtra.",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-15 14:34:19",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-17 12:45:54",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610887554,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610721259
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 17670113,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Please check the web site.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -35,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-03 02:42:47",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-10-31 07:44:40",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-03 02:42:47",
                    "question": "Hi Sir\n\nwhat is your room rate for double room with twin beds",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1635666280,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1635907367,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We do have rooms with bath tub in Taj Mahal Palace . In the Taj Mahal Tower we have only Apollo suites with bath tub .",
                    "naive_sentiment": -37,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 11:51:09",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 14564082,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628885004,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629028269,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 11:51:09",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-13 20:03:24",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "do you have bathtub 🛁",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly through your reservation messaging option.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:20:49",
                    "naive_sentiment": -39,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 15917073,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631566946,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712049,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:20:49",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-13 21:02:26",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hey I wana celebrate my partner's birthday there is any special facilities for the same ???"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612365744,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612539342,
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-03 15:22:24",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-05 15:35:42",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is gateway of india view can be captured from the room",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Yes you can click pictures from your mobile phone but you will have a top view.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -39,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-05 15:35:42",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 6883061,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1668106707,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677229402,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-11-10 18:58:27",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 09:03:22",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello we land at 1 am in the morning and we will likely be at the property around 3 am. Is that possible to check in at that time?",
                    "answer": "All arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 09:03:22",
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 32418480
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 14981432,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly refer to your package inclusions for the breakfast. The pool is non operations as per Government directives.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:55:09",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-22 12:34:35",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:55:09",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is breakfast included and is the pool functional",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629635675,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899709
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 15093618,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "You can certainly get a wine bottle from outside to consume in your room only.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:54:26",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-24 18:02:04",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:54:26",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Can I carry a bottle of wine from outside shop into my room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629828124,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899666
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 12761187,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:08:34",
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "answer": "Kindly contact the hotel directly. We have day use rooms for upto 5 hours only.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Can we checkinn at 11 am \nStay till 9 pm",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:08:34",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-12 10:52:12",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088114,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626087132
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611747344,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1611748881,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-27 11:35:44",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-27 12:01:21",
                    "question": "Is the pool operational,??",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Due to the pandemic the swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -41,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-27 12:01:21",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6735269
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1687060327,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1687240173,
                    "answered_at": "2023-06-20 05:49:33",
                    "asked_at": "2023-06-18 03:52:07",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Can I make a reservation for my parents where I make the entire payment upfront so that my parents are not bothered during their stay?",
                    "answer": "You may make the payment in advance towards room charges and taxes and an advance towards extras spend during the stay too ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-06-20 05:49:33",
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 37518881,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 18943851,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "A seperate room reservation will need to be made.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-10 12:18:44",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-10 12:18:44",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-09 07:05:33",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "do you have / provide bed for  drivers night stay arrangement ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639033533,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1639138724
                },
                {
                    "question": "If staying at the the tower is it possible to use the Taj Mahal pool?\nOr can you use the Taj Mahal hotel pool if you have lunch or a spa treatment?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-15 13:23:08",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-07 12:38:54",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1631712188,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1631018334,
                    "question_id": 15666503,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-15 13:23:08",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The pool services are non operational due to government policy."
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly contact our Catering Sales team directly by calling the hotel boardline.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -43,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:28:39",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 8096354,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616168770,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912919,
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:28:39",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-19 15:46:10",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "want to arrange a marriage involving 50 persons on 2nd May. Need a banquet hall. please quote with vegetarian lunch for 50 pax & other detail",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-08-28 04:33:43",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "answer": "Visitor are allowed from morning 0900 hrs. To 2000 hrs",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question_id": 39142102,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1693197223,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1692588985,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "What are visitors timing",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-08-28 04:33:43",
                    "asked_at": "2023-08-21 03:36:25"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:57:47",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Certain rooms have smart TV's.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "question_id": 19152526,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599067,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1639638227,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does this room have a smart TV ?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-16 07:03:47",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:57:47"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-02 05:21:53",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can make arrangements at cost as per the Celebration menu. Please do write to us directly from your booking to share the same.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 18637155,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638422513,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638128067,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi,\nis there any complimentary on birthday",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-02 05:21:53",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-28 19:34:27"
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-09 18:24:12",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:10:43",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does the Superior Room have Bath tub??",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625855052,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088243,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 12631842,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Please request the same when bookin",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:10:43",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:46:13",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-04 06:11:54",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do you have bathubs in each and every bathroom?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614838314,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951973,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 7636136,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Superior & Deluxe room categories only have walk in showers while the Apollo Suite and rooms at the Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai have bathtubs.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:46:13",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45
                },
                {
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 7635988,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:46:07",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Superior & Deluxe room categories only have walk in showers while the Apollo Suite and rooms at the Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai have bathtubs.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there is bath tub is available  in superiors city view rooms",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-04 06:00:00",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:46:07",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951967,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614837600
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422449,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1601839803,
                    "question": "I am booking a room for meeting.. My other 2 clients are allowed to visit me in my room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:14:09",
                    "asked_at": "2020-10-04 19:30:03",
                    "naive_sentiment": -45,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:14:09",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Non residential guests are not allowed on guest floors. You can meet them at the restaurant. A prior table reservation will be required for them to enter the hotel.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 4948003,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1653645377,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1653844063,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-29 17:07:43",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-27 09:56:17",
                    "question": "Hello,\nWe booked the non-board package.\nHow much will it cost to add only breakfast for one day per person ? \nThank you.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Breakfast will be chargeable at INR. 1200+18% taxes per person per day for our inhouse guests.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-29 17:07:43",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 25157991
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can assit with birthday celebrations at charge. Please do request the same from your booking. We can share the menu for your perusal.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:09:32",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 12731636,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626028869,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088172,
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-11 18:41:09",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:09:32",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hi, can we celebrate a birthday among two people only?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I have booked in 2 adults but booking is confirmed sand to my mail.1 parson please confirm tome",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-03 10:20:03",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:36:19",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831779,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1612347603,
                    "question_id": 6877495,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:36:19",
                    "naive_sentiment": -47,
                    "answer": "Please message directly from your booking.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629619153,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629899596,
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-22 07:59:13",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-25 13:53:16",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is outside liquor/food allowed to be taken into the room?",
                    "answer": "You can certianly get outside liquor and pre-manufactured food (like chips, etc) into the room only. However outside food from other restaurants, etc. is not allowed. Kindly contact the Duty Mnager/ Front Office team for further clarification.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-25 13:53:16",
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 14971114,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-04-13 04:00:42",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Dear guest, we do have vegetarina food at the hotel. Once the booking has been processed do mention your preference for vegetarian food to note the same.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 8782863,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1618286442,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1618248114,
                    "question": "Do you have proper pure vegetarian food ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-04-12 17:21:54",
                    "answered_at": "2021-04-13 04:00:42",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 5541831,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Breakfast can be ordered in the room on an A La Carte basis. In-room dining service will be available from 07:00 hrs. to 23:30 hrs.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-11-22 22:00:27",
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "answered_at": "2020-11-22 22:00:27",
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-22 15:41:23",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi my check in time is 2pm so will you be able to serve us breakfast in room ?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1606059683,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1606082427,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1603142989,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1603205588,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "asked_at": "2020-10-19 21:29:49",
                    "answered_at": "2020-10-20 14:53:08",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Can I get a smoking room?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Dear Guest, Kindly do request for the same once the booking has been made through the contact the hotel option.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-10-20 14:53:08",
                    "naive_sentiment": -49,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 5160587,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1652792240,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1652783473,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I am planning to book a room for a day in June. Would the hotel Be charging extra amount if we need the room decorated a little for Birthday purpose?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-05-17 10:31:13",
                    "answered_at": "2022-05-17 12:57:20",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-05-17 12:57:20",
                    "naive_sentiment": -51,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can make arrangements for a special occassion at an additional charge. Please contact the hotel directly for the details of the same.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 24686511,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1641411180,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644826932,
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-05 19:33:00",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:22:12",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Can you please clarify what do you mean when you say free public parking at location nearby? Is it a safe and secured parking?",
                    "answer": "The parking is around the hotel vicinity. For further queries kindly contact the Duty Manageer at the hotel directly.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:22:12",
                    "naive_sentiment": -51,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 19731643,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-13 19:48:01",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:24:44",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "wats they square foot of room",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636832881,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137484,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 18151367,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "The Superior Room City View King Bed is 26 m² or 279 sq ft.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -53,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:24:44"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Post booking, you can get in touch us and we can share the payment link.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:11:59",
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 20218909,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642613117,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830319,
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:11:59",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-19 17:25:17",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi there. I want to book a room for a couple as treat from me. I want to make full payment when I book it - prepayment, is that possible? Thanks"
                },
                {
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite or in the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:27:58",
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 8265811,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616664774,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912878,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:27:58",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-25 09:32:54",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there a bath tub in the room?"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:46:54",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-27 10:08:04",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "can I get my breakfast in bed?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614420484,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614952014,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 7498115,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answer": "It will be on an A La Carte basis at additional charge.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:46:54",
                    "naive_sentiment": -55
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611379719,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1612187473,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-23 05:28:39",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-01 13:51:13",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Appolo suit is in taj tower or taj palace",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-01 13:51:13",
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 6652846
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-14 11:09:51",
                    "naive_sentiment": -55,
                    "answer": "Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 6405815,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610622591,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610374535,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is this room the tower or mahal side ?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-11 14:15:35",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-14 11:09:51"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629028315,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628899892,
                    "question": "There is a bath tub in deluxe room?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 11:51:55",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-14 00:11:32",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": -59,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 11:51:55",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "No Deluxe rooms do not have bath tub , only Apoll suites in the Tower have bath tub.",
                    "question_id": 14572834,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 14007859,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Kindly do note Superior & Deluxe rooms, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Kindly contact the hotel directly for the 2nd query.\n",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-05 15:10:24",
                    "naive_sentiment": -59,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-05 15:10:24",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-03 20:48:32",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there bath tub in superior room? Which amenities are currently available?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628023712,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1628176224,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644661305,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827084,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-12 10:21:45",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:24:44",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello team,\nhow can I arrange a candle light dinner?",
                    "answer": "Please contact the Food 7 beverages team at the hotel boardline directly",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:24:44",
                    "naive_sentiment": -61,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 21097162
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1679032436,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1678967426,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "For 3 adults in one room is there an extra bed for the 3rd person\nAlso if we have breakfast and dinner included where is the dinner ? In any restaurant of our choosing ?\n",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-16 11:50:26",
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-17 05:53:56",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-17 05:53:56",
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Extra bed can be provided at an additional charge.\nDinner will be a set meal in a pre-designated venue",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 35257743,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 19404584,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 10:00:31",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Current guidelines in Maharashtra do not permit the usage of the swimming pool. The Gymnasium (lockers and changing facility) is operational from 07:00 to 22:00 hrs daily. The steam and shower facilities are currently not available as per guidelines.",
                    "question": "Hi\nAre the swimming pool and fitness centre open?  I am hoping to come in January or February 2022",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-26 17:54:01",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 10:00:31",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599231,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1640541241
                },
                {
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-19 05:50:09",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-20 13:11:43",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "I want a room for 4 adults or 2 rooms for 2 guests each.",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1629352209,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629465103,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 14833500,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answer": "Please book it via the site",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-20 13:11:43",
                    "naive_sentiment": -63
                },
                {
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Parking is around the hotel vicinity or the lane behind the hotel B K Boman Mehram Marg and is at the owner’s risk or alternately there is a BMC pay & park is available opposite Regal Cinema that you can opt for.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-17 14:25:51",
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 12985598,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1626422251,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626531951,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-17 14:25:51",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-16 07:57:31",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "car parking facility is available ? need to book for a day as my son is bored sitting in the house for more than a year now. please reply."
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -63,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-05 13:44:41",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "We can confirm an early check-in at 08:00 hrs at an addiitonal half day's charge. For Arrivals prior to 08:00 hrs you will have to pre-book your room from the previous night.",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 7556435,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1614951881,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1614606911,
                    "question": "We will be arriving at about 0300, is it possible to check in at 0600.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-05 13:44:41",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-01 13:55:11"
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677832086,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1677827576,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi, do your deluxe room sea view come in twin beds?",
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-03 07:12:56",
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-03 08:28:06",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-03 08:28:06",
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Deluxe room sea view category does not have twin bedded room. ",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 34954152,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-18 16:12:19",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Non resident guests are currently not allowed as per government policy.",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 9645974,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621354339,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1620509293,
                    "question": "Guest would be allowed during stay ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-08 21:28:13",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-18 16:12:19"
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5796560,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-11 13:47:15",
                    "naive_sentiment": -65,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The Superior and Deluxe categories have only a walk in shower and does not have a bathtub. The Apollo Suite has a bathtub and a walk in shower.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Bath tab is available in all the rooms or in deluxe and above??",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-11 13:47:15",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-09 17:17:39",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607694435,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1607534259
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040187,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628694259,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there a bathtub ? and is it a sea view ?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-11 15:04:19",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:09:47",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:09:47",
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "answer": " Superior and Deluxe room category at the Taj Mahal Tower, only has a walk-in shower. The bathtub is available in the Apollo Suite in the Taj Mahal Tower & the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai. Its is a City view room as per description.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 14438433,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "Will you provide a small complimentary birthday cake? for one of the guest's birthday?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-15 15:08:36",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-08 17:48:22",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1629040116,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1628444902,
                    "question_id": 14270881,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-15 15:08:36",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Celebrations can be arranged at an additional charge."
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831451,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608881241,
                    "question": "Is there a bath tub?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-25 07:27:21",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:30:51",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:30:51",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Only walk-in shower.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 6061173,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1
                },
                {
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "question_id": 6065939,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:30:46",
                    "naive_sentiment": -67,
                    "answer": "Only walk-in shower.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does this room have a bath tub?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:30:46",
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-25 15:19:47",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831446,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1608909587
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 8294874,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. At the Taj Mahal Tower we have limited interconnecting room sets in the Superior and Deluxe room categories with one room being a sea view and the other a city view.",
                    "naive_sentiment": -69,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:27:06",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:27:06",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-26 09:30:29",
                    "question": "Is the swimming pool operational and also do you have interconnecting rooms",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616751029,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912826,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Since we are arriving early morning in Bombay, would it be possible to check in at about 9:30- 10 am?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-16 20:32:35",
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-17 05:54:31",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1679032471,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1678998755,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 35268001,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-17 05:54:31",
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Arrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate",
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1638778564,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1638952382,
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-06 08:16:04",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-08 08:33:02",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hello,\n\nDo you have quarantine rooms? If yes how can we book it",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Please contact the hotel directly",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-08 08:33:02",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "question_id": 18852140,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1627822415,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1627905826,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-08-02 12:03:46",
                    "asked_at": "2021-08-01 12:53:35",
                    "question": "Free Parking within the hotel is available for guests?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please do note the Disinfection services for the vehicle with valet parking is available at a charge of INR 300 per visit. Parking is around the hotel vicinity or the lane behind the hotel B K Boman Mehram Marg and is at the owner’s risk. ",
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-08-02 12:03:46",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 13859921
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-03-28 06:28:07",
                    "naive_sentiment": -71,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is currently not operational and closed until further notice. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 8203913,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1616912887,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1616491867,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello is your swimming pool operational due to COVID ?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-03-23 09:31:07",
                    "answered_at": "2021-03-28 06:28:07",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1649772331,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830405,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:13:25",
                    "asked_at": "2022-04-12 14:05:31",
                    "question": "How about honeymoon suit? \nWhat are check-in and check-out charges? \nWhat are inclusions and exclusions after paying booking amount? \nWhat are the facilities with additional charges?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Please get in touch directly",
                    "naive_sentiment": -73,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:13:25",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 23221156
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1637137389,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1636687876,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "rate for buffet dinner",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-11-17 08:23:09",
                    "asked_at": "2021-11-12 03:31:16",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-11-17 08:23:09",
                    "naive_sentiment": -75,
                    "answer": "Please contact the Food & Beverages team by directly calling the hotel.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 18095810,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 26426182,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "px_upsort_covid_q_and_a_ds_model__would_resort": 1,
                    "naive_sentiment": -77,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:26:24",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Valet parking facility is available. Overnight parking is available at a charge",
                    "question": "Do u have parking facilities? Is valet parking chargeable ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-22 04:23:54",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:26:24",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234384,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1655871834
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "What are early checkin charges?",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-07-26 07:03:26",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:16:02",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233762,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1658819006,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 28270463,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:16:02",
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:13:01",
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-15 15:22:45",
                    "question": "If i arrived early around 10 am is it possible to check in?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660576965,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233581,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 29338209,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:13:01"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660327001,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233566,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:12:46",
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-12 17:56:41",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Hello, I’ll land at 4am is it possible to check in early morning?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:12:46",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 29207553,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:12:38",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "question_id": 29177621,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677233558,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1660284150,
                    "question": "can I check in at 10am in morning",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:12:38",
                    "asked_at": "2022-08-12 06:02:30",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:48:55",
                    "asked_at": "2023-01-02 22:53:51",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "We need 1 room for 3 days - but we will be arriving 5 am in morning. Can we get room at that time . After paying  some nominal charges",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1672700031,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228535,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 33522377,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "•\tAll arrivals before 08:00hrs are billed from the previous night. \n•\tArrivals between 08:00-10:00hrs will be charged 50% of the applicable rate and arrivals between 10:00-12:00hrs will be charged 25% of the applicable rate\n",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:48:55",
                    "naive_sentiment": -79
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 20178462,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:11:06",
                    "naive_sentiment": -79,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "At charge. Please revert from your booking directly.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello,\n\nDo you offer airport transfers?\n\nThanks.",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:11:06",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-18 16:41:14",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830266,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642524074
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 6151955,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available onli in the Apollo Suite at Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-14 11:07:42",
                    "naive_sentiment": -81,
                    "asked_at": "2020-12-29 18:27:43",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-14 11:07:42",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Does the bathroom have a bathtub",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1609266463,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610622462,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed"
                },
                {
                    "question": "do u have bathtub",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-13 13:30:21",
                    "answered_at": "2021-01-14 11:08:07",
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1610622487,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1610544621,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 6449006,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -83,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-01-14 11:08:07",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "The bathtub is available only in the Apollo Suite at Taj Mahal Tower, Mumbai and the rooms at The Taj Mahal Palace, Mumbai.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1684582360,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1684561278,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Person paying for one adult for a deluxe room, can be/she can invite guests?",
                    "answered_at": "2023-05-20 11:32:40",
                    "asked_at": "2023-05-20 05:41:18",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-05-20 11:32:40",
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "answer": "No visitors are allowed beyond 21:00hrs ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 36822492,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 30944842,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "answer": "No visitors are allowed beyond 21:00hrs ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 10:28:33",
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 10:28:33",
                    "asked_at": "2022-09-23 13:55:57",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi can my family visit me in my room when i am staying here?",
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1663941357,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677234513
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1654574358,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677227629,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:33:49",
                    "asked_at": "2022-06-07 03:59:18",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is there fen along with ac in room??",
                    "answer": "The rooms are air conditioned",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:33:49",
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 25675751,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644520334,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827174,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-10 19:12:14",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:26:14",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Is swimming pool usage available again?",
                    "answer": "The hotel is in the process of upgrading our product; swimming pool is under renovation till further notice.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:26:14",
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "question_id": 21043932
                },
                {
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-02-14 08:26:07",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The hotel is in the process of upgrading our product; swimming pool is under renovation till further notice.",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 21060495,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1644827167,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1644568987,
                    "question": "Is pool open ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-02-11 08:43:07",
                    "answered_at": "2022-02-14 08:26:07"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-07-12 11:11:16",
                    "asked_at": "2021-07-09 17:40:48",
                    "question": "guest are allow in room ???",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1625852448,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1626088276,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 12629838,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Non resident guests are not allowed in the guest rooms due to the current scenario as per hotel policy.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-07-12 11:11:16"
                },
                {
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-05-23 07:02:46",
                    "asked_at": "2021-05-21 19:59:22",
                    "question": "I am not able to find any room which has bathtub and also shower area",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1621627162,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1621753366,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 10171541,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Apollo Suite has a bath tub, walk-in shower and sea view. ",
                    "naive_sentiment": -85,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-05-23 07:02:46"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1676658391,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228457,
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:47:37",
                    "asked_at": "2023-02-17 18:26:31",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "hi. can you set up an extra bed for the 3rd adult ? or do you have rooms with 2 doubles ?",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The rooms can accommodate maximum 3 guests(including children). We can provide extra roll away bed at an additional charge.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:47:37",
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 34642877,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1630774600,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1630774878,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2021-09-04 16:56:40",
                    "answered_at": "2021-09-04 17:01:18",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do you have the facility for driver accommodation and whether driver can stay in car. Is the parking inside the premises",
                    "answer": "We do not have a facility for driver accomodation. An additional room will need to be booked.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-09-04 17:01:18",
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471708,
                    "question_id": 15556535
                },
                {
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hello. I would like to book a room for my friend who is visiting from the USA. What are the guidelines? Can he check in directly after arrival?",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-20 16:08:40",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:34:47",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831687,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611158920,
                    "question_id": 6604304,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:34:47",
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "answer": "Please do contact the hotel directly.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0
                },
                {
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Please do contact the hotel directly.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -87,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:34:40",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 6677144,
                    "room_id": 7471707,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1611497839,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "room_name": "Superior Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831680,
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:34:40",
                    "asked_at": "2021-01-24 14:17:19",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "Is there any discount for Indian Army soldiers ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null
                },
                {
                    "question": "Does the room have a bathtub ?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2023-03-10 11:09:38",
                    "answered_at": "2023-03-11 06:06:37",
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1678514797,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1678446578,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 35116170,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "naive_sentiment": -89,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-03-11 06:06:37",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "The Deluxe Room Sea view has a shower cubicle. It does not have bathtub",
                    "hotel_id": 74717
                },
                {
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-16 11:46:01",
                    "naive_sentiment": -89,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "•\tCheck-outs between 14:00-16:00hrs will be charged at 25% of the room rate, and those between 16:00-18:00hrs will be charged at 50% of the room rate.\n•\tAny departures post 18:00hrs will be charged for the full night.",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "question_id": 34415779,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1676547961,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1675833825,
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Hi. Is there an option of late check out? At what time would that be and what is the extra cost for it?",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-16 11:46:01",
                    "asked_at": "2023-02-08 05:23:45",
                    "language": "xu"
                },
                {
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1689188145,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room City View King Bed",
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1689417870,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2023-07-15 10:44:30",
                    "asked_at": "2023-07-12 18:55:45",
                    "question": "Can 3 adults and 1 child (5years old) stay in one Deluxe room? What are the charges for extra bed? Thanks",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Maximum 3 guest (including children) can be accommodated. For 3 adults and a child, 2 rooms need to be booked. ",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -91,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-07-15 10:44:30",
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "room_id": 7471705,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 38155996
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1640599179,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1640409290,
                    "question": "We are a family of 3. Do you have any rooms that can accommodate 3 adults?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-12-27 09:59:39",
                    "asked_at": "2021-12-25 05:14:50",
                    "naive_sentiment": -91,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-12-27 09:59:39",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "Our rooms can accomodate 3 adults as long as the booking is processed on triple occupancy except the Taj Club rooms.",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 19366730,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "question_id": 20053163,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "The swimming pool is operational from 0600 hours to 0900 hours, 12 noon to 1500 hours and 1800 hours to 2100 hours daily.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -93,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2022-04-13 06:10:42",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "asked_at": "2022-01-15 07:41:54",
                    "answered_at": "2022-04-13 06:10:42",
                    "question": "swimming pool is accessible",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1642232514,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1649830242,
                    "hidden": 0
                },
                {
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1607422511,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1604250616,
                    "question": "Hii i am coming from goa and my flight will arrive at 7 am. I need early checkin at 8 am.",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2020-12-08 10:15:11",
                    "asked_at": "2020-11-01 17:10:16",
                    "naive_sentiment": -95,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2020-12-08 10:15:11",
                    "votes": 0,
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "answer": "The same can be confirmed at an additional half days charge. Kindly do request the same on your booking request. ",
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "question_id": 5295525,
                    "translated_answer": null
                },
                {
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "question_id": 34028298,
                    "room_id": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answer": "Extra roll away bed can be provide maximum one, at an additional charge",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "naive_sentiment": -97,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2023-02-24 08:48:25",
                    "asked_at": "2023-01-23 11:35:52",
                    "answered_at": "2023-02-24 08:48:25",
                    "language": "xu",
                    "question": "is there extra beds?",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1674473752,
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1677228505
                },
                {
                    "answer": "Regret that Spa is not a part of the package.",
                    "hotel_id": 74717,
                    "votes": 0,
                    "answered_at_formatted": "2021-02-20 14:36:42",
                    "naive_sentiment": -97,
                    "translated_answer": null,
                    "sign_off": null,
                    "translated_question": null,
                    "room_id": 7471710,
                    "question_id": 7153398,
                    "ask_time_epoch": 1613312298,
                    "answer_time_epoch": 1613831802,
                    "room_name": "Deluxe Room Sea View King Bed",
                    "hidden": 0,
                    "language": "xu",
                    "answered_at": "2021-02-20 14:36:42",
                    "asked_at": "2021-02-14 14:18:18",
                    "is_or_could_be_translated": null,
                    "question": "Do you have sea view room spa packages for 1 night ?"
                }
            ],
            "opted_out_of_q_and_a": 0,
            "average_response_time_text": "Subject to availability at the property"
        }
    }
}